<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="side_stories">Side Stories</string>
    <string name="rougarou_scenario">Curse of the Rougarou</string>
    <string name="carnevale_scenario">Carnevale of Horrors</string>

    <!--Campaign log-->
    <string name="rougarou_alive">The Rougarou continues to haunt the bayou. Curse of the Rougarou weakness added to
        an investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_destroyed">The Rougarou is destroyed, and the curse is lifted. Lady Esprit added to an
        investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_escaped">The Rougarou escaped, and you embraced the curse. Curse of the Rougarou weakness
        and Monstrous Transformation added to an investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>

    <string name="carnevale_many_sacrificed">Many were sacrificed to Cnidathqua during the Carnevale. <i>Mask</i>
        card added to each investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_banished">The sun banished Cnidathqua into the depths. <i>Mask</i> card added to each
        investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_retreated">Cnidathqua retreated to nurse its wounds. <i>Mask</i> card added to each
        investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_sacrifice_made">Random basic <i>Madness</i>, <i>Injury</i>, or <i>Monster</i> weakness
        added to each investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_abbess_satisfied">Abbess Allegria Di Biase added to an investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>

    <!--Scenario introductions-->
    <string name="rougarou_introduction"><b>Terror Grips New Orleans!</b>\n
    \nMinnie Klein, your contact at the Arkham Advertiser, had slipped you a draft of the article over a cup of
        coffee at Velma\'s Diner. It would have gone to print had Doyle Jeffries, the lead editor, not scoffed at
        the concept. \"I believe his exact words were, \'I ain\'t printing the ravings of some Voodoo lunatic
        and passing it off as news,\'\" she explained. From the sly grin spreading across her face, you could
        tell she smelled a story.\n
    \nThe headline was sensationalist. Three killings in nine days was enough to spook a town, sure. But you
        doubt all of New Orleans is gripped by terror, or even knows about the killings. Still, something
        piqued your interest. \"Lady Esprit,\" the Voodoo priestess from the article, claimed that a malign
        curse had taken root in the bayou.\n
    \n\"There\'s something to this, isn\'t there? I know that look,\" Minnie said. You weren\'t sure. If Lady
        Esprit was right, this \"roux-ga-roux\" wouldn\'t stop killing at three, that\'s for sure. But curses?
        Wolf-people? How could such things be real? Only one way to find out. You put on your coat and head for
        the Northside station&#8230;</string>

    <string name="carnevale_introduction"><b>The Carnevale is Coming&#8230;</b>\n
    \n\"Look,\" Sheriff Engel insists, \"I know it sounds crazy, but that\'s all there is to it.\" He sighs and
    sits back down, pouring a cup of joe for you and one for himself. \"A dame in Uptown spotted a cracked egg
        wearing this mask and holdin\' a bloody butcher\'s cleaver,\" he says, motioning to the black leather
        mask sitting on his desk. It has a comically long nose and a strange symbol scrawled in yellow on its
        forehead. \"So, she calls it in. My boys and I picked him up on the corner of Saltonstall &amp;
        Garrison.\" The sheriff\'s jaw clenches and his brows furrow as he recounts the story. \"Fella did
        nothing but laugh as we slapped the bracelets on him. Called himself Zanni. Said nothing except the
        \'carnival is coming,\' whatever the hell that meant. Wasn\'t until the next day we found the victim\'s
    body. Defense wanted him in a straitjacket. We were happy to oblige.\"\n
    \nThere isn\'t much time to spare. If your research is right, there is more to this case than meets the eye
        . This \"Zanni\" wasn\'t talking about Darke\'s Carnival, but rather, the Carnevale of Venice, which
        begins just before the next full moon&#8230;</string>


    <!--Scenario setup instructions-->
    <string name="rougarou_sets">The Bayou.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_locations">Sort each of the locations into 4 piles, by trait (New Orleans,
        Riverside, Wilderness, and Unhallowed). Randomly choose 1 of these piles and remove those locations
        from the game. Randomly choose another 1 of these piles and put those locations into play.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play at a Bayou location in play.\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_set_aside">Curse of the Rougarou encounter set.\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_set_aside_two">Each location in the other 2 piles, Lady Esprit, Bear Trap, and Fishing Net.\n</string>

    <string name="carnevale_sets">Carnevale of Horrors</string>
    <string name="carnevale_locations">Choose 1 location at random and remove it from the game. If San Marco
        Basilica or Canal-side is chosen, randomly choose a different location instead.
        \nPut the other 8 locations into play, in a random circular formation.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play at San Marco Basilica.\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_set_aside">Cnidathqua, Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, and Gilded Volto.\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_additional">Put Abbess Allegria Di Biase into play at San Marco Basilica.\n
    \nShuffle the 7 Masked Carnevale-Goers and put 1 into play at each location other than San Marco Basilica,
        Masked Carnevale-Goer side face-up. Do not look at their other sides.</string>


    <!--Scenario Resolutions-->
    <string name="rougarou_no_resolution">Somehow, you manage to make it back to safety before daybreak,
        resting until late afternoon. It isn\'t until you seek out Lady Esprit the next day that you realize
        who last night\'s victim was. With a heavy heart and an unshakeable dread, you choose to bury her body
        instead of contacting the authorities - the less people who delve this deep into the bayou, the better.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_resolution_one">Somehow, you manage to make it back to safety before daybreak,
        resting until late afternoon. It isn\'t until you seek out Lady Esprit the next day that you realize
        who last night\'s victim was. With a heavy heart and an unshakeable dread, you choose to bury her body
        instead of contacting the authorities - the less people who delve this deep into the bayou, the better.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_resolution_two">The creature gives a pitiful wail as dark miry blood oozes from its
        wounds. By the time its body collapses into the mud, it has transformed back into its original form -
        the form of a young dark-skinned man, his expression twisted in agony. You bring his body back to Lady
        Esprit and she works her strange magic, removing the stain of the curse from the land. \"Call on me
        should you ever need my help,\" the mysterious woman tells you.\n
        \n<b>Remove the Curse of the Rougarou weakness from it\'s bearer\'s deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Lady Esprit to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="rougarou_resolution_three">Somehow, you have managed to quell the rage and bloodlust of the
        curse within the creature, and in moments the shape of a young, dark-skinned man stands before you,
        panting and sweating. He seems to only just now understand everything he\'s done, and agrees to flee to
    a secluded corner of the earth where he can harm no one. However, the curse lives on. He sees it in your
        eyes and grips your arm tightly. \"Don\'t let it take control,\" he warns. \"I was weak, but you - I
        can tell you are strong. Control the curse as I could not.\"\n
    \n<b>The bearer of the Curse of the Rougarou weakness must add Monstrous Transformation to his or her deck.</b></string>

    <string name="carnevale_no_resolution">You sputter awake as an oar gently taps your shoulder.
        \"<i>Tutto bene</i>?\" The gondolier holding the oar says with a concerned expression. You nod and drag
    yourself onto the docks from his gondola, drenched and aching all over. The city is devastated. Most of the
    boats in the canal are wrecked, and the streets are covered not in confetti, but in blood&#8230;\n
    \n<b>Move 1 Innocent Reveler from underneath the act deck to underneath the agenda deck, if able.</b>\n
    \n<b>In player order, each investigator may choose one of the following <i>Mask</i> cards to add to his or
            her deck: Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, or Gilded Volto.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the act deck and at least 1 underneath the agenda deck,
            select <i>Sacrifice Made</i>.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the agenda deck and 3 underneath the act deck, select
            <i>Abbess Satisfied</i>.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_resolution_one">The city is still recovering from the events during the eclipse.
        With nearly all evidence of the creature melted away by the hot sun, many attribute the violence during
    the Carnevale to local crime lord Cascio Di Boerio and his crew. Those that know the truth know better than
    the speak of the elder creature that lives in Laguna Veneta. With any luck, its name will never be spoken
        again.\n
    \n<b>In player order, each investigator may choose one of the following <i>Mask</i> cards to add to his or
            her deck: Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, or Gilded Volto.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the act deck and at least 1 underneath the agenda deck,
            select <i>Sacrifice Made</i>.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the agenda deck and 3 underneath the act deck, select
            <i>Abbess Satisfied</i>.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_resolution_two">The creature recoils as globules of its jelly-like flesh rip and
        tear from its body, splashing into the lagoon. It makes no sound as its torn body sinks into the depths
        . The chanting in the city plunges into mournful silence. As you return it to the canal-side streets,
        black feathers fall from the sky where bright confetti once fluttered. You can only wonder how long it
        will take for the creature to recover.\n
    \n<b>In player order, each investigator may choose one of the following <i>Mask</i> cards to add to his or
            her deck: Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, or Gilded Volto.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the act deck and at least 1 underneath the agenda deck,
            select <i>Sacrifice Made</i>.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the agenda deck and 3 underneath the act deck, select
            <i>Abbess Satisfied</i>.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_sacrifice">Sacrifice made</string>
    <string name="carnevale_reward_sacrifice">Too many lives were lost during the eclipse to stop the
        machinations of Cindathqua\'s servants. The beast has been fed, its minions empowered. You find
        yourself hoping you don\'t live long enough to see the fallout of your failure.\n
    \n<b>Each investigator searches the collection for a random basic <i>Madness</i>, <i>Injury</i>, or
            <i>Monster</i> weakness and adds it to his or her deck for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_abbess">Abbess satisfied</string>
    <string name="carnevale_reward_abbess">"<i>Grazie mille</i> - thank you for all your help,\" Allegria says
        as you return to the basilica. \"Thanks to you, there were few casualties. I shudder to think what
        might have happened had you not arrived. Should you ever require assistance, please do not hesitate to
        ask.\"\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Abbess Allegria Di Biase to his or her deck.</b></string>
</resources>