<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="night_campaign">Night of the Zealot</string>

    <string name="night_scenario_one">Scenario 1: The Gathering</string>
    <string name="night_scenario_two">Scenario 2: The Midnight Masks</string>
    <string name="night_scenario_three">Scenario 3: The Devourer Below</string>


    <!--Miscellaneous-->
    <string name="ghoul_priest_additional">Shuffle the Ghoul Priest into the encounter deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="ghoul_priest_checkbox">Ghoul Priest killed</string>
    <string name="cultists_interrogated">Cultists interrogated: \n</string>
    <string name="cultists_interrogated_resolution">Cultists interrogated</string>
    <string name="cultists_got_away">\nCultists got away: \n</string>
    <string name="drew">"Wolf-Man" Drew</string>
    <string name="herman">Herman Collins</string>
    <string name="peter">Peter Warren</string>
    <string name="victoria">Victoria Devereux</string>
    <string name="ruth">Ruth Turner</string>
    <string name="masked_hunter">The Masked Hunter</string>

    <!--Campaign log-->
    <string name="house_standing">Your house is still standing.\n\n</string>
    <string name="house_burned">Your house has burned to the ground.\n\n</string>
    <string name="ghoul_priest_alive">The Ghoul Priest is still alive.\n\n</string>
    <string name="lita_forced">Lita was forced to find others to help her cause.\n\n</string>
    <string name="past_midnight">It is past midnight.\n\n</string>
    <string name="drew_log">\t\t"Wolf-Man" Drew\n</string>
    <string name="herman_log">\t\tHerman Collins\n</string>
    <string name="peter_log">\t\tPeter Warren\n</string>
    <string name="victoria_log">\t\tVictoria Devereux\n</string>
    <string name="ruth_log">\t\tRuth Turner\n</string>
    <string name="masked_hunter_log">\t\tThe Masked Hunter\n</string>
    <string name="no_cultist">\t\tNone\n</string>
    <string name="umordhoth_succumbed">\nArkham succumbed to Umordhoth\'s terrible vengeance.\n</string>
    <string name="umordhoth_broken">\nThe ritual to summon Umordhoth was broken.\n</string>
    <string name="umordhoth_repelled">\nThe investigators repelled Umordhoth.\n</string>
    <string name="umordhoth_sacrificed">\nThe investigators sacrificed Lita Chantler to Umordhoth.\n</string>

    <!--Edit log-->
    <string name="house_heading">Your house</string>
    <string name="ghoul_heading">Ghoul Priest</string>
    <string name="ghoul_priest_dead">The Ghoul Priest was killed.</string>
    <string name="lita_heading">Lita Chantler</string>
    <string name="lita_not_obtained">You did not join Lita to help her cause.</string>
    <string name="lita_obtained">You joined Lita to help her cause.</string>
    <string name="midnight_heading">Midnight</string>
    <string name="not_past_midnight">It is not past midnight.</string>
    <string name="conclusion">Campaign Conclusion</string>


    <!--Chaos bag-->
    <string name="gathering_skull_one">-X. X is the number of <b><i>Ghoul</i></b> enemies at your location.</string>
    <string name="gathering_skull_two">-2. If you fail, after this skill test, search the encounter deck and discard
        pile for a <b><i>Ghoul</i></b> enemy, and draw it. Shuffle the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="gathering_cultist_one">-1. If you fail, take 1 horror.</string>
    <string name="gathering_cultist_two">Reveal another token. If you fail, take 2 horror.</string>
    <string name="gathering_tablet_one">-2. If there is a <b><i>Ghoul</i></b> enemy at your location, take 1 damage.</string>
    <string name="gathering_tablet_two">-4. If there is a <b><i>Ghoul</i></b> enemy at your location, take 1 damage and 1 horror.</string>

    <string name="midnight_skull_one">-X. X is the highest number of doom on a <b><i>Cultist</i></b> enemy in play.</string>
    <string name="midnight_skull_two">-X. X is the total number of doom in play.</string>
    <string name="midnight_cultist_one">-2. Place 1 doom on the nearest <b><i>Cultist</i></b> enemy.</string>
    <string name="midnight_cultist_two">-2. Place 1 doom on each <b><i>Cultist</i></b> enemy in play. If there are no
        <b><i>Cultist</i></b> enemies in play, reveal another token.</string>
    <string name="midnight_tablet_one">-3. If you fail, place 1 of your clues on your location.</string>
    <string name="midnight_tablet_two">-4. If you fail, place all your clues on your location.</string>

    <string name="devourer_skull_one">-X. X is the number of <b><i>Monster</i></b> enemies in play.</string>
    <string name="devourer_skull_two">-3. If you fail, after this skill test, search the encounter deck and discard
        pile for a <b><i>Monster</i></b> enemy, and draw it. Shuffle the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="devourer_cultist_one">-2. Place 1 doom on the nearest enemy.</string>
    <string name="devourer_cultist_two">-4. Place 2 doom on the nearest enemy.</string>
    <string name="devourer_tablet_one">-3. If there is a <b><i>Monster</i></b> enemy at your location, take 1 damage.</string>
    <string name="devourer_tablet_two">-5. If there is a <b><i>Monster</i></b> enemy at your location, take 1 damage and 1 horror.</string>
    <string name="devourer_thing_one">-5. If there is an <b><i>Ancient One</i></b> enemy in play, reveal another token.</string>
    <string name="devourer_thing_two">-7. If there is an <b><i>Ancient One</i></b> enemy in play, reveal another token.</string>


    <!--Campaign introduction-->
    <string name="night_introduction"><b>The Ghouls Hunger…</b>\n
        \nFriday, September 18, 1925. Arkham, Massachusetts. It is the end of a long and
        abnormally hot summer. The first hints of autumn beckon, but a heavy heat persists, relentless. A silent,
        unspoken anger grips the town. Tempers are short, and in the last week alone there have been numerous reports
        of townspeople coming to heated, violent blows with one another over simple misunderstandings.\n
    \nAnd now, a call from James Hankerson. He claims to have found a dismembered body in his barn.\n
    \nBlaming the weather would be too easy. There is something wrong with this town, and not a whole lot this old
        soothsayer can do to stop the slide. My auguries indicate a small group of investigators will soon take note
        of these strange happenings and set forth to make things right. I’ll be watching their progress…but I won’t
        be holding my breath.</string>


    <!--Scenario introductions-->
    <string name="gathering_introduction">You and your partners have been investigating strange events taking place
        in your home city of Arkham, Massachusetts. Over the past few weeks, several townspeople have mysteriously
        gone missing. Recently, their corpses turned up in the woods, savaged and half-eaten. The police and
        newspapers have stated that wild animals are responsible, but you believe there is something else going on.
        You are gathered together at the lead investigator’s home to discuss these bizarre events.</string>

    <string name="midnight_introduction_one">The woman came to you in a panic, raving about monsters emerging from the
        ground in a home near Rivertown. “I managed to trap them,” she explains, “but there are others. Other pits.
        Other domains.” Only last week, you would have thought she was a lunatic. Recent events, however, have
        challenged your preconceptions of normality. You decide to hear her out.\n
    \nShe introduces herself as Lita Chantler and lays out a tale that strains the limits of your belief. “The
        creatures I speak of ,” she claims, “are called ghouls—cruel beings who plague the crypts, caverns, and
        tunnels beneath the city of Arkham…”\n
    \n“These creatures feed on the corpses of humans, and they are served by a dark cult within Arkham whose members
        have inexplicably come to worship the ancient master of the ghouls. This cult has been killing innocent
        people and feeding them to the ghouls, satiating a monstrous hunger. A dark balance was maintained. Until
        now. Recently,” Lita continues, “one of their lairs, where the corpses were stored, was destroyed. Since
        then, the ghouls have been more active than usual. I have tracked their movements and tried my best to stop
        them from running amok throughout the city. But I think there is something worse going on. The cult has been
        planning something darker, and more ominous, than anything I have yet observed. Indications are that this
        plan shall come to fruition tonight, shortly after midnight. Beyond that, I cannot fathom what to expect.\n
    \n“Many of the cultists,” Lita continues, “will seem like everyday people, despite their foul intentions.
        Whenever the cult meets, its members don masks shaped like the skulls of various animals to protect their
        identities from one another. These masks are our mark. Symbols of death and decay. We must unmask the
        cultists to expose and derail their plans. We have but a few hours. The more cultists we find before
        midnight, the better.”</string>
    <string name="midnight_introduction_two">In the wake of the disaster at your home, Lita Chantler, the red-haired
        woman from your parlor, lays out a tale that—even in light of what you have just witnessed—strains the limits
        of your belief. “The creatures in your home,” she claims, “are called ghouls—cruel beings who plague the
        crypts, caverns, and tunnels beneath the city of Arkham…”\n
    \n“These creatures feed on the corpses of humans, and they are served by a dark cult within Arkham whose members
        have inexplicably come to worship the ancient master of the ghouls. This cult has been killing innocent
        people and feeding them to the ghouls, satiating a monstrous hunger. A dark balance was maintained. Until
        now. Recently,” Lita continues, “one of their lairs, where the corpses were stored, was destroyed. Since
        then, the ghouls have been more active than usual. I have tracked their movements and tried my best to stop
        them from running amok throughout the city. But I think there is something worse going on. The cult has been
        planning something darker, and more ominous, than anything I have yet observed. Indications are that this
        plan shall come to fruition tonight, shortly after midnight. Beyond that, I cannot fathom what to expect.\n
    \n“Many of the cultists,” Lita continues, “will seem like everyday people, despite their foul intentions.
        Whenever the cult meets, its members don masks shaped like the skulls of various animals to protect their
        identities from one another. These masks are our mark. Symbols of death and decay. We must unmask the
        cultists to expose and derail their plans. We have but a few hours. The more cultists we find before
        midnight, the better.”</string>

    <string name="devourer_introduction">After a frantic nighttime search throughout Arkham, you have tracked down
        and questioned several members of the cult. Your findings are disturbing: they claim to worship a being known
        as Umôrdhoth, a monstrous entity from another realm.\n
    \nYou are able to confirm much of Lita’s story: the cult is agitated over the destruction of a ghoul lair.
        However, a surprising detail also turns up: the one who invaded the lair and set this night’s events in
        motion was none other than Lita Chantler herself! You are not sure why this important detail was omitted from
        Lita’s story—did she tell you only as much as was necessary to draw you into her conflict? But in another
        light, she seems to be fighting to protect the city of Arkham from a terrible menace.\n
    \nThe final piece of the puzzle was found written in a journal possessed by one of the cultists. It describes a
        dark ritual to be performed deep within the woods south of Arkham, this very night. According to the journal,
        the ritual’s completion will open a gate and bring forth the cult’s dark master into this world. “If the cult
        is not stopped,” Lita warns, “there is a possibility that Umôrdhoth’s vengeance will consume all in its
        path.” Frightened but determined to stop the ritual, you head into the woods…</string>


    <!--Scenario setup instructions-->
    <string name="gathering_sets">The Gathering, Rats, Ghouls, Striking Fear, Ancient Evils, and Chilling Cold.</string>
    <string name="gathering_locations">Put the Study location into play.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play in the Study.\n</string>
    <string name="gathering_set_aside">All other locations, the Ghoul Priest and Lita Chantler.\n</string>

    <string name="midnight_sets">The Midnight Masks, Chilling Cold, Nightgaunts, Dark Cult, and Locked Doors.</string>
    <string name="midnight_locations">Choose one of the two Downtown locations and one of the two Southside
        locations at random and put them into play. Remove the other versions of Downtown and Southside from
        the game.\n
        \nPut the Northside, Easttown, Rivertown, St. Mary\'s Hospital, Graveyard, Miskatonic
        University, and Your House locations into play.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play at Your House.\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_locations_no_house">Choose one of the two Downtown locations and one of the two Southside
        locations at random and put them into play. Remove the other versions of Downtown and Southside from
        the game.\n
        \nPut the Northside, Easttown, Rivertown, St. Mary\'s Hospital, Graveyard, and Miskatonic
        University locations into play.\n
        \nRemove Your House from the game.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play at Rivertown.\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_set_aside">Cult of Umordhoth encounter set as a separate \"Cultist
        Deck\".\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_additional_two">Search the gathered encounter sets for 1 copy of Acolyte and spawn
        it at Southside.\n\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_additional_three">Search the gathered encounter sets for 2 copies of Acolyte. Spawn
        1 at Southside and 1 at Downtown.\n\n</string>
    <string name="midnight_additional_four">Search the gathered encounter sets for 3 copies of Acolyte. Spawn
        1 at Southside,  1 at Downtown, and 1 at the Graveyard.\n\n</string>

    <string name="devourer_sets">The Devourer Below, Ancient Evils, Striking Fear, Ghouls, and Dark
        Cult.</string>
    <string name="devourer_sets_two">Randomly choose one of the following 4 encounter sets:\n
    \nAgents of Yog-Sothoth, Agents of Shub-Niggurath, Agents of Cthulhu, or Agents of Hastur.</string>
    <string name="devourer_locations">Put the Main Path location into play. Shuffle the 6 copies of Arkham
        Woods, choose 4 of them at random, and put them into play without looking at their revealed sides.
        Remove the other 2 from the game.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play at the Main Path.\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_set_aside">The Ritual Site and Umordhoth cards.\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_additional">Add 1 Elder Thing chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the
        campaign.\n\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_additional_midnight">Each player discards 2 random cards from his or her starting
        hand.\n\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_cultists_one">Place 1 doom on Agenda 1a.\n\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_cultists_two">Place 2 doom on Agenda 1a.\n\n</string>
    <string name="devourer_cultists_three">Place 3 doom on Agenda 1a.\n\n</string>


    <!--Scenario resolutions-->
    <string name="gathering_no_resolution">You barely manage to escape your house with your lives. The woman from
        your parlor follows you out the front door, slamming it behind her. “You fools! See what you have done?” She
        pushes a chair in front of the door, lodging it beneath the doorknob. “We must get out of here. Come with me,
        and I will tell you what I know. We are the only ones who can stop the threat that lurks beneath from being
        unleashed throughout the city.” You’re in no state to argue. Nodding, you follow the woman as she runs from
        your front porch out into the rainy street, toward Rivertown.\n
    \n<b>The lead investigator earns the Lita Chantler card.</b></string>
    <string name="gathering_resolution_one">You nod and allow the red-haired woman to set the walls and floor of your
        house ablaze. The fire spreads quickly, and you run out the front door to avoid being caught in the inferno.
        From the sidewalk, you watch as everything you own is consumed by the flames. “Come with me,” the woman says.
        “You must be told of the threat that lurks below. Alone, we are surely doomed…but together, we can stop it
        .”\n
    \n<b>The lead investigator earns the Lita Chantler card.</b></string>
    <string name="gathering_resolution_two">You refuse to follow the overzealous woman’s order and kick her out of
        your home for fear that she will set it ablaze without your permission. “Fools! You are making a grave
        mistake!” she warns. “You do not understand the threat that lurks below…the grave danger we are all in!”
        Still shaken by the night’s events, you decide to hear the woman out. Perhaps she can shed some light on
        these bizarre events…but she doesn’t seem to trust you very much.</string>
    <string name="gathering_resolution_three">You run to the hallway to try to find a way to escape the house, but
        the burning-hot barrier still blocks your path. Trapped, the horde of feral creatures that have invaded your
        home close in, and you have nowhere to run.\n
    \n<b>All investigators who haven’t resigned are killed.</b>\n
    \n<b>If the lead investigator is killed, choose an investigator to earn the Lita Chantler card.</b></string>

    <string name="midnight_no_resolution">You’ve managed to obtain some useful information about the cult and its
        plans. You can only hope it’s enough.</string>
    <string name="midnight_resolution_one">You’ve managed to obtain some useful information about the cult and its
        plans. You can only hope it’s enough.</string>
    <string name="midnight_resolution_two">Twelve bells ring out, signaling midnight. You’re out of time; the cult’s
        ritual will begin shortly. You’ve managed to obtain some useful information about the cult and its plans. You
        can only hope it’s enough.</string>

    <string name="devourer_no_resolution">Too frightened to face her fate, Lita flees into the night. She realizes
        that she has failed and Umôrdhoth’s vengeance will pursue her wherever she goes. The creature’s tendrils
        spread throughout the city of Arkham, searching for her. It lurks in the darkness of every corner, tugging at
        the seams of reality. But Lita is nowhere to be found, so the creature dwells in the shadows to this day,
        searching…killing.\n
    \n<b>The investigators lose.</b></string>
    <string name="devourer_resolution_one">You have managed to prevent the cult from summoning its master. Although
        you’re unsure what would have happened had the cult succeeded, you’re relieved that—at least for the time
        being—Arkham is safe. You capture as many cultists as you can find, but very few townspeople believe your
        tale. Perhaps it was all in your head, after all.\n
    \n<b>The investigators win!</b></string>
    <string name="devourer_resolution_two">Through force of arms and strength of will, you are somehow able to harm
        Umôrdhoth enough to send it reeling back to the dimension from which it emerged. Warmth and light return to
        the woods as the void-like mass is sucked in upon itself, vanishing in an instant. You aren’t sure if a being
        such as this can be killed, but for the time being it seems to have retreated. As their master vanishes, the
        ghouls nearby climb into the open pit below, fleeing with terrible cries and shrieks. You have stopped an
        evil plot, but the fight has taken its toll on your body and mind. Worse, you can’t help but feel
        insignificant in the face of the world’s mysteries. What other terrors exist in the deep, dark corners of
        reality?\n
    \n<b>The investigators win!</b></string>
    <string name="devourer_resolution_three">In the face of this horror, you don’t believe there is anything you can
        do to stop it. You have but one hope if you are to survive. You turn on Lita and throw her at the terrible
        monstrosity, watching in dread as its swirling void-like mass consumes her. She cries out in torment as the
        life is sucked from her body. “Umôrdhoth…Umôrdhoth…” the cultists chant. Lita Chantler vanishes without a
        trace. For a moment, you fear that the creature will now turn on you, but you hear one of the cultists say,
        “Umôrdhoth is a just god who claims only the guilty and the dead. Go, and you shall be spared.” The
        swirling mass vanishes, and warmth and light return to the woods. The cultists slink away, leaving you alive.
        Lita’s last moments are forever etched upon your memory.\n
    \n<b>The guilt over sacrificing Lita forever haunts your memory. Each investigator must search the collection for
            a random Madness weakness and add it to his or her deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>The investigators have survived, but their actions weigh heavily on their consciences.</b></string>
</resources>