<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="side_stories">Side Stories</string>
    <string name="rougarou_scenario">Curse of the Rougarou</string>
    <string name="carnevale_scenario">Carnevale of Horrors</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_scenario">Labyrinths of Lunacy</string>

    <string name="group_a">Group A</string>
    <string name="group_b">Group B</string>
    <string name="group_c">Group C</string>
    <string name="act_two_setup">Act 2 Setup</string>
    <string name="act_three_setup">Act 3 Setup</string>

    <!--Campaign log-->
    <string name="rougarou_alive">The Rougarou continues to haunt the bayou. Curse of the Rougarou weakness added to
        an investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_destroyed">The Rougarou is destroyed, and the curse is lifted. Lady Esprit added to an
        investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_escaped">The Rougarou escaped, and you embraced the curse. Curse of the Rougarou weakness
        and Monstrous Transformation added to an investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>

    <string name="carnevale_many_sacrificed">Many were sacrificed to Cnidathqua during the Carnevale. <i>Mask</i>
        card added to each investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_banished">The sun banished Cnidathqua into the depths. <i>Mask</i> card added to each
        investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_retreated">Cnidathqua retreated to nurse its wounds. <i>Mask</i> card added to each
        investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="no_reward">No additional cards added.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_sacrifice_made">Random basic <i>Madness</i>, <i>Injury</i>, or <i>Monster</i> weakness
        added to each investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_abbess_satisfied">Abbess Allegria Di Biase added to an investigator\'s deck.\n\n</string>


    <!--Chaos bag-->
    <string name="rougarou_skull_one">-2 (-4 instead if you are at a <b><i>Bayou</i></b> location).</string>
    <string name="rougarou_skull_two">-3 (-6 instead if you are at a <b><i>Bayou</i></b> location).</string>
    <string name="rougarou_cultist_one">-2. If the Rougarou is in your location, reveal another token.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_cultist_two">-3. If the Rougarou is in your location, reveal another token.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_tablet_one">Reveal another token. If you fail, until the end of the round, you cannot move.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_tablet_two">Reveal another token. If you fail, until the end of the round, you cannot move.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_thing_one">-4. If the Rougarou is at your location, it attacks you.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_thing_two">-4. If the Rougarou is at your location or a connecting location, it attacks you.</string>

    <string name="carnevale_skull_one">-2. This token has an additional -1 for each Innocent Reveler underneath the agenda deck.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_skull_two">-2. This token has an additional -1 for each Innocent Reveler underneath the act or agenda decks.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_cultist_one">Reveal another token. If you fail this test, draw the top card of the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_cultist_two">Reveal another token. If you fail this test, draw the top card of the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_tablet_one">-3. If you fail, deal 1 damage or 1 horror to the nearest Innocent Reveler in play.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_tablet_two">-4. Deal 1 damage or 1 horror to the nearest Innocent Reveler in play.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_thing_one">-4. If you fail and Cnidathqua is in play, it attacks you.</string>
    <string name="carnevale_thing_two">-6. If you fail and Cnidathqua is in play, it attacks you.</string>

    <string name="labyrinths_skull_one">–1. Reveal another token.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_skull_two">–1. Reveal another token. If you fail, you must either take 1 damage or 1 horror.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_cultist_one">–3. If you fail, place 1 of your clues on your location.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_cultist_two">–3. Place 1 of your clues on your location.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_tablet_one">–4. If you fail, lose 2 resources.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_tablet_two">–4. Lose 2 resources.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_thing_one">–4. If you fail, discard a random card from your hand.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_thing_two">–4. Discard a random card from your hand.</string>



    <!--Scenario introductions-->
    <string name="rougarou_introduction"><b>Terror Grips New Orleans!</b>\n
    \nMinnie Klein, your contact at the Arkham Advertiser, had slipped you a draft of the article over a cup of
        coffee at Velma\'s Diner. It would have gone to print had Doyle Jeffries, the lead editor, not scoffed at
        the concept. \"I believe his exact words were, \'I ain\'t printing the ravings of some Voodoo lunatic
        and passing it off as news,\'\" she explained. From the sly grin spreading across her face, you could
        tell she smelled a story.\n
    \nThe headline was sensationalist. Three killings in nine days was enough to spook a town, sure. But you
        doubt all of New Orleans is gripped by terror, or even knows about the killings. Still, something
        piqued your interest. \"Lady Esprit,\" the Voodoo priestess from the article, claimed that a malign
        curse had taken root in the bayou.\n
    \n\"There\'s something to this, isn\'t there? I know that look,\" Minnie said. You weren\'t sure. If Lady
        Esprit was right, this \"roux-ga-roux\" wouldn\'t stop killing at three, that\'s for sure. But curses?
        Wolf-people? How could such things be real? Only one way to find out. You put on your coat and head for
        the Northside station&#8230;</string>

    <string name="carnevale_introduction"><b>The Carnevale is Coming&#8230;</b>\n
    \n\"Look,\" Sheriff Engel insists, \"I know it sounds crazy, but that\'s all there is to it.\" He sighs and
    sits back down, pouring a cup of joe for you and one for himself. \"A dame in Uptown spotted a cracked egg
        wearing this mask and holdin\' a bloody butcher\'s cleaver,\" he says, motioning to the black leather
        mask sitting on his desk. It has a comically long nose and a strange symbol scrawled in yellow on its
        forehead. \"So, she calls it in. My boys and I picked him up on the corner of Saltonstall &amp;
        Garrison.\" The sheriff\'s jaw clenches and his brows furrow as he recounts the story. \"Fella did
        nothing but laugh as we slapped the bracelets on him. Called himself Zanni. Said nothing except the
        \'carnival is coming,\' whatever the hell that meant. Wasn\'t until the next day we found the victim\'s
    body. Defense wanted him in a straitjacket. We were happy to oblige.\"\n
    \nThere isn\'t much time to spare. If your research is right, there is more to this case than meets the eye
        . This \"Zanni\" wasn\'t talking about Darke\'s Carnival, but rather, the Carnevale of Venice, which
        begins just before the next full moon&#8230;</string>

    <string name="labyrinths_a_introduction">You wake up and realize you are in a strange place, with no memory of
        how you arrived. Your muscles are weak and uncooperative. Your vision is blurred. Simply rising to your feet
        takes a tremendous effort. Your legs are wobbly and can barely support your weight.\n
    \nFor the first time since awakening, you study your surroundings. You have been sealed in a windowless chamber,
        which is filled with copper pipes. The faint whistling of escaping air surrounds you on all sides. You are a
        prisoner here, with no means of escape. There is a note lying on the ground nearby. It reads:\n
    \nGreetings.\n
    \nI have gathered you here as an experiment. Think of this as a test of human will. You will survive. Or you will
        die.\n
    \nYou are not alone. Two other groups share in your fate. Will you risk your lives to aid them? Or will you find
        freedom upon the backs of their corpses?\n
    \nI will allow you to escape, should you prove strong of will and quick of wit. If not, your pain and anguish
        shall serve as a reminder that humans are not the inheritors of Earth.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_b_introduction">You wake up and realize you are in a strange place, with no memory of
        how you arrived. Your muscles are weak and uncooperative. Your vision is blurred. Simply rising to your feet
        takes a tremendous effort. Your legs are wobbly and can barely support your weight.\n
    \nFor the first time since awakening, you study your surroundings. You have been sealed in a windowless chamber,
        which is filled with copper pipes. The faint whistling of escaping air surrounds you on all sides. You are a
        prisoner here, with no means of escape. There is a note lying on the ground nearby. It reads:\n
    \nGreetings.\n
    \nI have gathered you here as an experiment. Think of this as a test of human will. You will survive. Or you will
        die.\n
    \nYou are not alone. Two other groups share in your fate. Will you risk your lives to aid them? Or will you find
        freedom upon the backs of their corpses?\n
    \nI will allow you to escape, should you prove strong of will and quick of wit. If not, your pain and anguish
        shall serve as a reminder that humans are not the inheritors of Earth.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_c_introduction">You wake up and realize you are in a strange place, with no memory of
        how you arrived. Your muscles are weak and uncooperative. Your vision is blurred. Simply rising to your feet
        takes a tremendous effort. Your legs are wobbly and can barely support your weight.\n
    \nFor the first time since awakening, you study your surroundings. You are in a dark chamber, lit only by a few
        candles. Old barrels, crates and rotten storage shelves fill the cramped chamber. You cannot see any windows
        or doors leading out. You are a prisoner here, with no means of escape. There is a note lying on the ground
        nearby. It reads:\n
    \nGreetings.\n
    \nI have gathered you here as an experiment. Think of this as a test of human will. You will survive. Or you will
        die.\n
    \nYou are not alone. Two other groups share in your fate. Will you risk your lives to aid them? Or will you find
        freedom upon the backs of their corpses?\n
    \nI will allow you to escape, should you prove strong of will and quick of wit. If not, your pain and anguish
        shall serve as a reminder that humans are not the inheritors of Earth.</string>


    <!--Scenario setup instructions-->
    <string name="rougarou_sets">The Bayou</string>
    <string name="rougarou_locations">Sort each of the locations into 4 piles, by trait (New Orleans,
        Riverside, Wilderness, and Unhallowed). Randomly choose 1 of these piles and remove those locations
        from the game. Randomly choose another 1 of these piles and put those locations into play.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play at a Bayou location in play.\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_set_aside">Curse of the Rougarou encounter set.\n</string>
    <string name="rougarou_set_aside_two">Each location in the other 2 piles, Lady Esprit, Bear Trap, and Fishing Net.\n</string>

    <string name="carnevale_sets">Carnevale of Horrors</string>
    <string name="carnevale_locations">Choose 1 location at random and remove it from the game. If San Marco
        Basilica or Canal-side is chosen, randomly choose a different location instead.
        \nPut the other 8 locations into play, in a random circular formation.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play at San Marco Basilica.\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_set_aside">Cnidathqua, Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, and Gilded Volto.\n</string>
    <string name="carnevale_additional">Put Abbess Allegria Di Biase into play at San Marco Basilica.\n
    \nShuffle the 7 Masked Carnevale-Goers and put 1 into play at each location other than San Marco Basilica,
        Masked Carnevale-Goer side face-up. Do not look at their other sides.</string>

    <string name="labyrinths_sets">The Labyrinths of Lunacy</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_sets_two">Only use the cards from the <i>Single Group</i> or from the <i>Epic
        Multiplayer</i> encounter set and remove all cards from the other set from the game, depending on if you are
        playing in <i>Single Group Mode</i> or <i>Epic Multiplayer Mode</i> respectively.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_set_aside">Key of Mysteries, Mysterious Syringe, Eixodolon, Eixodolon’s Pet, Rot
        Diagram, Hunger Diagram, Decay Diagram, both copies of Faceless Abductor, and each other location.\n
        \nIf you are playing in <i>Epic Multiplayer Mode</i>, also set The Jailor enemy and each double-sided story
        card aside, out of play.\n</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_a_locations">Randomly choose 1 of the 3 copies of Chamber of Secrets to put into play.
        Remove the other 2 copies from the game.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play in the Chamber of Secrets.\n</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_a_additional">Construct the act deck using only the (Group A) versions of Acts 1 and 2.
        Remove each other version of those acts from the game.\n
    \nThe lead investigator takes control of Eixodolon’s Note.\n
    \nAdd 2 Elder Thing tokens to the chaos bag.\n
        \nIf you are playing in <i>Single Group Mode</i>, put the set-aside Key of Mysteries into play in the Chamber of
        Secrets.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_a_locations_two">Put the 3 set-aside Labyrinthine Halls into play.\n
    \nPut the set-aside Chamber of Decay into play.\n</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_a_additional_two">Shuffle each set-aside Faceless Abductor and the encounter discard
        pile into the encounter deck.\n
    \nRemove all doom from play and proceed to Act 2a &amp; Agenda 2a.\n
        \nIf you are playing <i>Epic Multiplayer Mode</i>, choose one of the 3 groups at random. That group shuffles
        the set-aside The Jailor enemy into the encounter deck.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_locations_three">Put the set-aside Abandoned Warehouse into play.\n
    \nDisengage all engaged enemies and move each surviving investigator to the Abandoned Warehouse.\n</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_additional_three">Put the set-aside Eixodolon enemy into play at the Abandoned
        Warehouse.\n
    \nRemove all doom from play and proceed to Act 3a &amp; Agenda 3a</string>

    <string name="labyrinths_b_locations">Put the Chamber of Rain and Chamber of Sorrows locations into play.\n
        \nRandomly choose an investigator to begin play in the Chamber of Rain. Each other investigator begins play
        in the Chamber of Sorrows.\n</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_b_additional">Construct the act deck using only the (Group B) versions of Acts 1 and 2.
        Remove each other version of those acts from the game.\n
    \nThe lead investigator takes control of Eixodolon’s Note.\n
    \nAdd 2 Tablet tokens to the chaos bag.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_b_locations_two">Put the 3 set-aside Labyrinthine Halls into play.\n
    \nPut the set-aside Chamber of Rot and Chamber of Poison locations into play.\n</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_b_additional_two">Shuffle each set-aside Faceless Abductor and the encounter discard
        pile into the encounter deck.\n
    \nRemove all doom from play and proceed to Act 2a &amp; Agenda 2a.</string>

    <string name="labyrinths_c_locations">Put the Chamber of Night and Chamber of Regret locations into play.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play at the Chamber of Night.\n</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_c_additional">Construct the act deck using only the (Group C) versions of Acts 1 and 2.
        Remove each other version of those acts from the game.\n
    \nThe lead investigator takes control of Eixodolon’s Note.\n
    \nAdd 2 Cultist tokens to the chaos bag.\n
        \nIf you are playing in <i>Single Group Mode</i>, randomly choose 1 of the 3 set-aside copies of Chamber of
        Secrets and place it underneath the scenario reference card, without looking at its revealed side.</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_c_locations_two">Put the 3 set-aside Labyrinthine Halls into play.\n
    \nPut the set-aside Chamber of Hunger into play.\n</string>
    <string name="labyrinths_c_additional_two">Shuffle each set-aside Faceless Abductor and the encounter discard
        pile into the encounter deck.\n
    \nRemove all doom from play and proceed to Act 2a &amp; Agenda 2a.\n
    \nPut the set-aside Eixodolon’s Pet into play, near the Chamber of Hunger, but not at any location. While it is
        not at any location, it is considered to be “locked away.”</string>


    <!--Scenario Resolutions-->
    <string name="rougarou_no_resolution">Somehow, you manage to make it back to safety before daybreak,
        resting until late afternoon. It isn\'t until you seek out Lady Esprit the next day that you realize
        who last night\'s victim was. With a heavy heart and an unshakeable dread, you choose to bury her body
        instead of contacting the authorities - the less people who delve this deep into the bayou, the better.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_resolution_one">Somehow, you manage to make it back to safety before daybreak,
        resting until late afternoon. It isn\'t until you seek out Lady Esprit the next day that you realize
        who last night\'s victim was. With a heavy heart and an unshakeable dread, you choose to bury her body
        instead of contacting the authorities - the less people who delve this deep into the bayou, the better.</string>
    <string name="rougarou_resolution_two">The creature gives a pitiful wail as dark miry blood oozes from its
        wounds. By the time its body collapses into the mud, it has transformed back into its original form -
        the form of a young dark-skinned man, his expression twisted in agony. You bring his body back to Lady
        Esprit and she works her strange magic, removing the stain of the curse from the land. \"Call on me
        should you ever need my help,\" the mysterious woman tells you.\n
        \n<b>Remove the Curse of the Rougarou weakness from it\'s bearer\'s deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Lady Esprit to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="rougarou_resolution_three">Somehow, you have managed to quell the rage and bloodlust of the
        curse within the creature, and in moments the shape of a young, dark-skinned man stands before you,
        panting and sweating. He seems to only just now understand everything he\'s done, and agrees to flee to
    a secluded corner of the earth where he can harm no one. However, the curse lives on. He sees it in your
        eyes and grips your arm tightly. \"Don\'t let it take control,\" he warns. \"I was weak, but you - I
        can tell you are strong. Control the curse as I could not.\"\n
    \n<b>The bearer of the Curse of the Rougarou weakness must add Monstrous Transformation to his or her deck.</b></string>

    <string name="carnevale_no_resolution">You sputter awake as an oar gently taps your shoulder.
        \"<i>Tutto bene</i>?\" The gondolier holding the oar says with a concerned expression. You nod and drag
    yourself onto the docks from his gondola, drenched and aching all over. The city is devastated. Most of the
    boats in the canal are wrecked, and the streets are covered not in confetti, but in blood&#8230;\n
    \n<b>Move 1 Innocent Reveler from underneath the act deck to underneath the agenda deck, if able.</b>\n
    \n<b>In player order, each investigator may choose one of the following <i>Mask</i> cards to add to his or
            her deck: Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, or Gilded Volto.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the act deck and at least 1 underneath the agenda deck,
            select <i>Sacrifice Made</i>.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the agenda deck and 3 underneath the act deck, select
            <i>Abbess Satisfied</i>.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_resolution_one">The city is still recovering from the events during the eclipse.
        With nearly all evidence of the creature melted away by the hot sun, many attribute the violence during
    the Carnevale to local crime lord Cascio Di Boerio and his crew. Those that know the truth know better than
    the speak of the elder creature that lives in Laguna Veneta. With any luck, its name will never be spoken
        again.\n
    \n<b>In player order, each investigator may choose one of the following <i>Mask</i> cards to add to his or
            her deck: Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, or Gilded Volto.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the act deck and at least 1 underneath the agenda deck,
            select <i>Sacrifice Made</i>.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the agenda deck and 3 underneath the act deck, select
            <i>Abbess Satisfied</i>.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_resolution_two">The creature recoils as globules of its jelly-like flesh rip and
        tear from its body, splashing into the lagoon. It makes no sound as its torn body sinks into the depths
        . The chanting in the city plunges into mournful silence. As you return it to the canal-side streets,
        black feathers fall from the sky where bright confetti once fluttered. You can only wonder how long it
        will take for the creature to recover.\n
    \n<b>In player order, each investigator may choose one of the following <i>Mask</i> cards to add to his or
            her deck: Pantalone, Medico Della Peste, Bauta, or Gilded Volto.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the act deck and at least 1 underneath the agenda deck,
            select <i>Sacrifice Made</i>.</b>\n
    \n<b>If there are no Innocent Revelers underneath the agenda deck and 3 underneath the act deck, select
            <i>Abbess Satisfied</i>.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_sacrifice">Sacrifice made</string>
    <string name="carnevale_reward_sacrifice">Too many lives were lost during the eclipse to stop the
        machinations of Cindathqua\'s servants. The beast has been fed, its minions empowered. You find
        yourself hoping you don\'t live long enough to see the fallout of your failure.\n
    \n<b>Each investigator searches the collection for a random basic <i>Madness</i>, <i>Injury</i>, or
            <i>Monster</i> weakness and adds it to his or her deck for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="carnevale_abbess">Abbess satisfied</string>
    <string name="carnevale_reward_abbess">"<i>Grazie mille</i> - thank you for all your help,\" Allegria says
        as you return to the basilica. \"Thanks to you, there were few casualties. I shudder to think what
        might have happened had you not arrived. Should you ever require assistance, please do not hesitate to
        ask.\"\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Abbess Allegria Di Biase to his or her deck.</b></string>

    <string name="labyrinths_resolution_one">In the wrong hands, your anguish is a powerful weapon. Your blood fuels
        the arcane glyph carved into the cement floor at the labyrinth’s core. For the cruel mastermind who trapped
        you here, it is a moment of triumph and vindication. The entire world will feel this pain. This fear. This
        despair.\n
    \n<b>The investigators lose.</b></string>
    <string name="labyrinths_resolution_two">The mastermind falls to his knees, his mask cracked. Blood drips from
        his open wounds onto the cement floor. “Do you really think you can escape?” he wheezes. His distorted voice
        is pained but triumphant. “Do you really think… I would ever let you leave this place?” His body collapses to
        the ground. Seeing an opportunity to escape, you rush to the iron doors sealing you in the warehouse. With a
        desperate effort, you are finally able to break the padlock and push open the heavy doors.\n
    \nA sudden gust of cold evening air sweeps over you. You are surprised to see wooden docks on the side of the
        Miskatonic River. A few ducks quack in surprise and swim away from the nearest dock. Water sloshes along the
        shore. You hear dockworkers going about their business, their work day almost finished as the sun sets to
        your left. After taking a few steps, you collapse to the ground. You are too exhausted and injured to go on.
        “Who’s that?” a dockworker calls out. “Someone is hurt—quick, let’s get them to St. Mary’s!” You drift into
        unconsciousness just as a muscled man lifts you into his arms.\n
    \nYou wake up and realize you are in a strange place, with no memory of how you arrived. Your muscles are weak
        and uncooperative. Your vision is blurred. Simply rising to your feet takes a tremendous effort. Your legs
        are wobbly and can barely support your weight. A note on the ground nearby reads:\n
    \nGreetings. I have gathered you here as an experiment. Think of this as a test of human will. You will survive.
        Or you will die…\n
    \n<b>The investigators survived, but in another timeline, the labyrinth has a new guest.</b></string>
    <string name="labyrinths_resolution_three">The mastermind falls to his knees, his mask cracked. Blood drips from
        his open wounds onto the cement floor. “Do you really think you can kill me?” he wheezes. His distorted voice
        is pained but proud. “I am everywhere and everywhen. This vessel is but one. There are others. And if even
        one of them is proven right, I will never truly die.” His body falls limply to the ground. Seeing an
        opportunity to escape, you rush to the iron doors sealing you in the warehouse. With a desperate effort, you
        are finally able to break the padlock and push open the heavy doors.\n
    \nA sudden gust of cold evening air sweeps over you. You are surprised to see wooden docks on the side of the
        Miskatonic River. A few ducks quack in surprise and swim away from the nearest dock. Water sloshes along the
        shore. You hear dockworkers going about their business, their work day almost finished as the sun sets to
        your left. After taking a few steps, you collapse to the ground. You are too exhausted and injured to go on.
        “Who’s that?” a dockworker calls out. “Someone is hurt—quick, let’s get them to St. Mary’s!” A muscled man
        lifts you into his arms, and you are driven to the hospital.\n
    \nYou have somehow made it out of your captor’s hellish labyrinth, but his dying words haunt your thoughts. What
        did he mean by “others?” You recall the strange visions you saw in his maze, and a terrible thought seeps
        into your mind. The kidnapper had mentioned other groups, but you were never able to find them, and you have
        no idea if they made it out alive. You tell the police there are others and insist that they search the
        docks, but there is no trace of the warehouse you had escaped, nor of the mastermind who trapped you
        there…\n
    \n<b>The investigators survived, but Eixodolon lives on.</b></string>
    <string name="labyrinths_resolution_four">The mastermind falls to his knees, his mask cracked. Blood drips from
        his open wounds onto the cement floor. The outline of his body twists and blurs, like a wrinkle in the fabric
        of space and time. “So, the ritual has failed!” His bitter cackle descends into a cry of pain. “Perhaps
        humanity has a chance after all. This agony, this suffering! Such power is not meant for humans to wield. It
        is for the ones beyond!” He gasps and wheezes, collapsing to the ground. “Do not follow the path I followed,”
        he begs, “it leads only to… despair.” His breathing stops.\n
    \nYou have somehow defeated your captor, but many questions remain. Deciding to explore the labyrinth further,
        you find a way to break open the iron doors leading into the other sections of the complex. To your surprise,
        you find no other victims trapped in the labyrinth—only signs of their struggles, and of their survival.\n
    \nIt takes only one solid strike to break open the padlock sealing the warehouse’s iron doors. The sound of metal
        slamming against metal is tripled in its volume. You do not believe your kidnapper meant for you to ever
        leave, but somehow you have defied the odds stacked against you. You wonder if the others are opening these
        heavy doors at this very moment, too.\n
    \nA sudden gust of cold evening air sweeps over you. You are surprised to see wooden docks on the side of the
        Miskatonic River. A few ducks quack in surprise and swim away from the nearest dock. Water sloshes along the
        shore. You hear dockworkers going about their business, their work day almost finished as the sun sets to
        your left. You watch the sun disappear under the horizon, and the others watch in turn.\n
    \n<b>The investigators win!</b></string>
</resources>