<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="dunwich_campaign">The Dunwich Legacy</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_one">Scenario 1-A: Extracurricular Activity</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_two">Scenario 1-B: The House Always Wins</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_three">Scenario 2: The Miskatonic Museum</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_four">Scenario 3: The Essex County Express</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_five">Scenario 4: Blood on the Altar</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_six">Scenario 5: Undimensioned and Unseen</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_seven">Scenario 6: Where Doom Awaits</string>
    <string name="dunwich_scenario_eight">Scenario 7: Lost in Time and Space</string>
    <string name="dunwich_interlude_one">Interlude 1: Armitage\'s Fate</string>
    <string name="dunwich_interlude_two">Interlude 2: The Survivors</string>
    <string name="dunwich_epilogue">Epilogue</string>


    <!--Miscellaneous-->
    <string name="cheated_checkbox">An investigator \"cheated\"</string>
    <string name="cheated_text"><b>Add 1 Elder Thing chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the
        campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="adam_lynch_harold_walsted">Adam Lynch or Harold Walsted left play</string>
    <string name="engine_car_investigator">Investigator to enter Engine Car</string>
    <string name="engine_car_dodge">Failed to dodge the creature</string>
    <string name="engine_car_endure">Failed to endure the creature\'s extreme heat</string>
    <string name="kidnapped_cards">Stolen/Kidnapped Cards</string>
    <string name="necronomicon_defeated">Investigator with The Necronomicon (<i>Olaus Wormius Translation</i>)
        was defeated</string>
    <string name="armitage_defeated">Investigator with the Dr. Henry Armitage card was defeated</string>
    <string name="rice_defeated">Investigator with the Professor Warren Rice card was defeated</string>
    <string name="morgan_defeated">Investigator with the Dr. Francis Morgan card was defeated</string>
    <string name="remove_necronomicon"><b>Remove The Necronomicon (<i>Olaus Wormius Translation</i>) from the
        relevant investigator\'s deck.</b>\n\n</string>
    <string name="remove_armitage"><b>Remove the Dr. Henry Armitage card from the relevant investigator\'s deck
        .</b>\n\n</string>
    <string name="remove_rice"><b>Remove the Professor Warren Rice card from the relevant investigator\'s deck
        .</b>\n\n</string>
    <string name="remove_morgan"><b>Remove the Dr. Francis Morgan card from the relevant investigator\'s deck.</b>\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="underneath_agenda_deck">Underneath the agenda deck</string>
    <string name="henry_armitage">Dr. Henry Armitage</string>
    <string name="warren_rice">Professor Warren Rice</string>
    <string name="francis_morgan">Dr. Francis Morgan</string>
    <string name="zebulon_whateley">Zebulon Whateley</string>
    <string name="earl_sawyer">Earl Sawyer</string>
    <string name="another_ally">Another ally</string>
    <string name="brood_escaped_counter">Brood Escaped:</string>
    <string name="act_one_two_three">Finished at Act 1, 2 or 3</string>
    <string name="act_four">Finished at Act 4</string>


    <!--Campaign log-->
    <string name="investigators_unconscious">The investigators were unconscious for several hours.\n\n</string>
    <string name="warren_kidnapped">Professor Warren Rice was kidnapped.\n\n</string>
    <string name="warren_rescued">The investigators rescued Professor Warren Rice.\n\n</string>
    <string name="warren_sacrificed">Professor Warren Rice was sacrificed to Yog-Sothoth.\n\n</string>
    <string name="warren_survived">Professor Warren Rice survived The Dunwich Legacy.\n\n</string>
    <string name="students_failed">The investigators failed to save the students.\n\n</string>
    <string name="students_rescued">The students were rescued.\n\n</string>
    <string name="experiment_defeated">The Experiment was defeated.\n\n</string>
    <string name="obannion_failed">The O\'Bannion gang has a bone to pick with the investigators.\n\n</string>
    <string name="obannion_succeeded">Naomi has the investigators\' backs.\n\n</string>
    <string name="morgan_kidnapped">Dr. Francis Morgan was kidnapped.\n\n</string>
    <string name="morgan_rescued">The investigators rescued Dr. Francis Morgan.\n\n</string>
    <string name="morgan_sacrificed">Dr. Francis Morgan was sacrificed to Yog-Sothoth.\n\n</string>
    <string name="morgan_survived">Dr. Francis Morgan survived The Dunwich Legacy.\n\n</string>
    <string name="armitage_kidnapped">Dr. Henry Armitage was kidnapped.\n\n</string>
    <string name="armitage_rescued">The investigators rescued Dr. Henry Armitage.\n\n</string>
    <string name="armitage_sacrificed">Dr. Henry Armitage was sacrificed to Yog-Sothoth.\n\n</string>
    <string name="armitage_survived">Dr. Henry Armitage survived The Dunwich Legacy.\n\n</string>
    <string name="necronomicon_failed">The investigators failed to recover the <i>Necronomicon</i>.\n\n</string>
    <string name="necronomicon_destroyed">The investigators destroyed the <i>Necronomicon</i>.\n\n</string>
    <string name="necronomicon_taken">The investigators took custody of the <i>Necronomicon</i>.\n\n</string>
    <string name="necronomicon_stolen">The Necronomicon was stolen.\n\n</string>
    <string name="investigators_delayed">The investigators were delayed on their way to Dunwich.\n\n</string>
    <string name="silas_ritual">The ritual was completed.\n\n</string>
    <string name="silas_misery">The investigators put Silas Bishop out of his misery.\n\n</string>
    <string name="silas_restored">The investigators restored Silas Bishop.\n\n</string>
    <string name="silas_banished">The investigators banished Silas Bishop.\n\n</string>
    <string name="zebulon_sacrificed">Zebulon Whateley was sacrificed to Yog-Sothoth.\n\n</string>
    <string name="zebulon_survived">Zebulon Whateley survived The Dunwich Legacy.\n\n</string>
    <string name="sawyer_sacrificed">Earl Sawyer was sacrificed to Yog-Sothoth.\n\n</string>
    <string name="sawyer_survived">Earl Sawyer survived The Dunwich Legacy.\n\n</string>
    <string name="ally_sacrificed">An ally was sacrificed to Yog-Sothoth.\n\n</string>
    <string name="townsfolk_calmed">You calmed the townsfolk.\n\n</string>
    <string name="townsfolk_warned">You warned the townsfolk.\n\n</string>
    <string name="brood_escaped"> brood escaped into the wild.\n\n</string>
    <string name="investigators_entered_gate">The investigators entered the gate.\n\n</string>
    <string name="yog_tore_barrier">Yog-Sothoth tore apart the barrier between worlds, and became one
        with all reality.\n\n</string>
    <string name="closed_tear">The investigators closed the tear in reality.\n\n</string>
    <string name="yog_fled">Yog-Sothoth has fled to another dimension.\n\n</string>


    <!--Campaign introduction-->
    <string name="dunwich_introduction"><b>Prologue</b>\n
    \nDr. Henry Armitage pours himself a glass of pinot and sits down at his desk, gesturing for you to sit across
        from him. “I apologize for the short notice,” he begins. His face is pale, his forehead sweaty and wrinkled
        with worry.\n
    \nArmitage—the head librarian of Miskatonic University, and a former mentor of yours—privately contacted you in
        the hopes of gaining your assistance. Eager to help, you made your way to his home in Southside. Upon
        entering, you were surprised to find his home in disarray. Books and notes litter his desk, and an empty
        bottle of wine has tipped over onto the ground by the fireplace. You’d always known Armitage to be neat and
        well-organized.\n
    \nThe elderly man takes a moment to collect his thoughts. “I am looking for two of my colleagues—Dr. Francis
        Morgan, professor of archaeology, and Warren Rice, professor of languages. Warren was supposed to meet up
        with me over supper earlier today to discuss several important findings, but he has since gone missing. At
        first I thought nothing of it, but I have a nagging feeling something else is going on. A very…<b>familiar</b>
        feeling.” You’ve never seen Armitage quite this worried before. His hands tremble as he reaches for the glass
        on his desk, and he sips from it nervously. “I tried to find Francis, hoping he knew where Warren was, but he
        too is out of touch. Francis has been spending a lot of time in some gambling den, or so I am told.\n
    \n“I sent for you because I am worried Warren might be in trouble. I would appreciate it greatly if you could
        find him for me. You may also wish to ask Francis for help, if you can reach him.”</string>
    <string name="dunwich_start_option_one">Professor Warren Rice was last seen working late at night in the
        humanities department of Miskatonic University. Let’s search for him there.</string>
    <string name="dunwich_start_option_two">Dr. Francis Morgan was last seen gambling at the Clover Club, an upscale
        speakeasy and gambling joint located downtown. Let’s go talk to him.</string>


    <!--Scenario introductions-->
    <string name="extracurricular_introduction">Dr. Armitage is worried his colleague, Professor Warren Rice, might
        be in trouble, so he has asked for your help in finding his friend. He seems unreasonably nervous about his
        colleague’s disappearance considering Professor Rice has only been “missing” for a matter of hours…</string>

    <string name="house_introduction">Dr. Armitage suggested you track down his associate Dr. Francis Morgan. He’s
        not sure whether Dr. Morgan is in trouble, but he’s not particularly happy with his colleague’s present
        choice of company. He’s in the Clover Club, a notorious gambling joint somewhere downtown. Finding the club’s
        exact location isn’t easy—you have to grease a few palms just to learn which of the Downtown restaurants
        operates as the club’s front. That restaurant is La Bella Luna, a somewhat upscale Italian eatery by the
        theatre. You change into your Sunday best and make your way there.\n
    \nIn front of La Bella Luna stands a man in a pinstripe suit who sizes you up as you approach. “Enjoy
        yourselves,” he says with a snake-like grin as he holds open the restaurant’s front door.</string>

    <string name="armitage_interlude_one">You are more than a little rattled by your experiences in the university and
        the Clover Club. You’re not sure what to make of whoever—or whatever—was after Rice and Morgan. Worried about
        Dr. Armitage, you swiftly make your way back to his home. When you arrive, you find that the latches of his
        front door have been busted open, and his living area and study have been ransacked. Dr. Armitage is nowhere
        to be found. Searching his home, you find a journal the intruders didn’t steal tucked beneath several other
        documents in the bottom drawer of Armitage’s desk. The journal appears to be written in a strange language
        you cannot decode, using a script you’ve never seen in your entire life. Fortunately, it seems Dr. Armitage
        had already gone through the trouble of translating it into English. Apparently, it belongs to one “Wilbur
        Whateley.”\n
    \nThe journal—along with Armitage’s many notes—tells a startling tale, one you would scarcely believe had it not
        been for your harrowing experiences earlier tonight…</string>
    <string name="armitage_interlude_two">When you arrive at Dr. Armitage’s home in Southside, you find him sitting at
        his desk, pale-faced and sweating with worry. He is grateful to you for searching for his colleagues, but he
        doesn’t look relieved. With a long pause, he straightens his glasses and explains:\n
    \n“I’m afraid I must apologize. There’s something I didn’t mention to you earlier.” Dr. Armitage then spins a
        tale you would scarcely believe had it not been for your harrowing experiences earlier that night…\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Dr. Henry Armitage to his or her deck.</b></string>

    <string name="miskatonic_introduction_one">Several months ago, Armitage and his colleagues stopped a rampaging
        horror from tearing through Dunwich, a backwater town several hours north and west of Arkham. At first you
        imagine this beast as a rabid bear, or worse, but the professor’s description of the creature paints a
        different picture.\n
    \nIt all began when a man named Wilbur Whateley entered the Orne Library looking for Olaus Wormius’s Latin
        translation of a book called the Necronomicon. Wilbur already possessed a beaten-up English translation by
        Dr. John Dee, but it was insufficient for his purposes. Armitage turned the man away, fearing what use the
        strange man had for the book. Whateley returned in secret, hoping to steal the book, but was attacked by a
        hound guarding the university. Armitage, Rice, and Morgan later discovered Whateley’s body. A description of
        the foul corpse—semi-anthropomorphic and covered in fur, with a leathery hide and greenish-grey
        tentacles—causes you to question whether or not Whateley was truly human.\n
    \nThe notes written by Dr. Armitage in the journal stress Whateley’s desire to get his hands on the Necronomicon
        for some terrible purpose. As you read on, it seems that Dr. Armitage brought the university’s copy of the
        tome to Harold Walsted—the curator of the Miskatonic Museum—for safekeeping in the museum’s Restricted Hall.
        Although you are worried about your mentor, you are equally worried that Armitage’s kidnappers might get
        their hands on this Necronomicon. You decide to head to the museum to prevent them from acquiring it.</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_introduction_two">Several months ago, Armitage and his colleagues stopped a rampaging
        horror from tearing through Dunwich, a backwater town several hours north and west of Arkham. At first you
        imagine this beast as a rabid bear, or worse, but the professor’s description of the creature paints a
        different picture.\n
    \nIt all began when a man named Wilbur Whateley entered the Orne Library looking for Olaus Wormius’s Latin
        translation of a book called the Necronomicon. Wilbur already possessed a beaten-up English translation by
        Dr. John Dee, but it was insufficient for his purposes. Armitage turned the man away, fearing what use the
        strange man had for the book. Whateley returned in secret, hoping to steal the book, but was attacked by a
        hound guarding the university. Armitage, Rice, and Morgan later discovered Whateley’s body. A description of
        the foul corpse—semi-anthropomorphic and covered in fur, with a leathery hide and greenish-grey
        tentacles—causes you to question whether or not Whateley was truly human.\n
    \n“My colleagues and I were quick to put the ordeal behind us,” Armitage says with a sigh. “But it seems that
        things haven’t fully resolved themselves. I’ll tell you the rest later, but for now, it is imperative that we
        get our hands on that copy of the Necronomicon. If my instincts are correct, the assailants you’ve
        encountered will be searching for it. After all that transpired, I didn’t feel safe keeping it at the
        library, so I brought it to my good friend, Harold Walsted. He is the current curator of the Miskatonic
        Museum. I thought it would be safe in the museum’s Restricted Hall, but now I’m not so sure. You must
        retrieve it at all costs! I fear terribly what they could do with the rites contained in its pages…”</string>

    <string name="essex_introduction">Recent events in the Museum have forced you to re-evaluate Armitage’s tale
        about Dunwich. It cannot be a coincidence—Wilbur Whateley, the Necronomicon, the creature from Dunwich, and
        the people and creatures who attacked here in Arkham—everything must be connected. You’re certain now where
        you must head: the lonely and dismal town of Dunwich Village.\n
    \nYou consider telling the Massachusetts State Police what you know, but the negative consequences outweigh the
        potential gain. Given the nature of your story, they would likely write your stories off as an absurd hoax.
        Worse, they could lock you up. After all, you were present in an illegal speakeasy, and you also trespassed
        in the museum. Instead, you decide to head to Dunwich yourself, in order to investigate further.\n
    \nYou pack everything you think you might need and manage to get some rest for the night. In the morning, you
        head to the train station in Northside and purchase a last-minute express ticket. Dunwich is several hours by
        train northwest along the Miskatonic River Valley. There is no train station in Dunwich, but you manage to
        phone one of Armitage’s acquaintances in the small village: a man by the name of Zebulon Whateley who was
        present during the events several months ago.\n
    \nArmitage’s notes indicate that the Whateley family is spread across many branches, some decadent and
        unscrupulous, others “undecayed” or otherwise untouched by nefarious and diabolic rites. According to
        Armitage, Zebulon’s branch of the family lay somewhere between the decayed and undecayed Whateleys, who knew
        of the traditions of his ancestors, but was not corrupted by them. He agrees to pick you up at the closest
        station and drive you into town.\n
    \nAs the train departs from Arkham, you feel the events of the previous night catching up to you, and exhaustion
        sets in. But before you can safely reach your destination, the train car suddenly rumbles and shakes,
        startling you out of your reverie. The train loudly skids to a violent halt, and you hear a rattling noise
        behind you…</string>

    <string name="blood_introduction">When you finally reach Dunwich, you are greeted by Zebulon Whateley and Earl
        Sawyer, another man from the village who had met with Dr. Armitage during the incident several months ago.
        “Things ain’t lookin’ too good here,” Earl tells you. “Some folk up and went missin’ a few nights ago. ‘Dem
        whippoorwills won’ shut up. Dunno what yer doin’ here, but last time you Arkham folk came ‘round it was bad
        news. Very bad news.” His eyes blink rapidly, and he coughs and looks away.\n
    \n“Look, why don’t you rest fer the night an’ look fer whatever it is yer looking fer t’morra,” Zebulon chimes
        in, putting a wrinkled hand on your shoulder. You begin to protest, but your aching muscles and weary mind
        won’t allow you to refuse. The elderly man offers to take you in for the night, and drives you to his home at
        the outskirts of Dunwich village. The town is disheveled and eerie, and you find yourself wishing you hadn’t
        come here at all. You fall asleep on the ride over and scarcely remember anything else from that night.\n
    \nWhen you awaken, you find that Zebulon’s house is abandoned, and there is no sign of the elderly man, or of Mr.
        Sawyer. Fearing the worst, you head into the village of Dunwich to investigate, hoping to find answers.</string>

    <string name="survivors_interlude">Inside the chamber that contained the terrible beast, you find the missing
        townsfolk and the others from Arkham; they are bound and shackled. You also find several documents that
        suggest the creature you found isn’t the only one of its kind in Dunwich. You free the creature’s victims
        from their bonds, and they offer you their thanks. You begin to plan your next move.</string>
    <string name="survivors_interlude_one">\n“It is far worse than we had thought,” Dr. Armitage says, pale and
        trembling. “Wilbur Whateley was only the beginning. There were more, many more in Dunwich, who knew of the
        ‘Great Old Ones’ and who desired power and knowledge above all else, the Earth be damned. I knew I should
        have burned that wretch’s journal. But thanks to its contents, I know how we can stop them. We are the only
        ones who can! Now quickly, help me with this solution—the powder is the key, yes, the powder is the only
        way…”\n
    \n<b>If the Dr. Henry Armitage card is not already in an investigator’s deck, any one investigator may choose to
            add that card to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="survivors_interlude_two">\nProfessor Rice adjusts his glasses and studies the documents and arcane
        manuscripts left in the chamber. “I thought this nightmare was over and done with,” he sighs. “But we have a
        duty to see this through. We have to stop these creatures, or it won’t be just Dunwich in trouble. The powder
        mixture Armitage created to see the creatures will be our saving grace,” he explains, and sets off to the
        task of recreating the powder.\n
    \n<b>If the Professor Warren Rice card is not already in an investigator’s deck, any one investigator may choose
            to add that card to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="survivors_interlude_three">\n“Thank you for everything you’ve done,” Dr. Morgan says, taking count
        of your provisions and ammunition. “Last time, we needed some of that strange powder Armitage concocted to
        even see the beast that terrorized Dunwich. If there’s more of those things out there, we’re going to need
        that powder. I think I remember how he made it…”\n
    \n<b>If the Dr. Francis Morgan card is not already in an investigator’s deck, any one investigator may choose to
            add that card to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="survivors_interlude_four">\n“Dunwich’s had its fair share of oddities,” Zebulon explains to you
        with a quavering voice, “but I ain’t ever seen anything as sick and twisted as this…this…<b>thing</b>.” He
        gives the creature’s remains one last sickened glance before closing the door to the chamber behind him,
        shuddering. He locks eyes with you, his expression grim. “Whoever dun this gotta pay. I’ll do all I can to
        help.”\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add the Zebulon Whateley card to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="survivors_interlude_five">\n“I never could’a made it if it weren’t for you,” Earl says with a
        stammer, shaking your hand repeatedly. “If ’n there’s anything I can do to repay yeh, just ask away. I ain’t
        much of a fighter or anythin’, but I’ll do all I can. Jus’…don’t make me look at anythin’ like that <b>beast
        </b> again, a’right?”\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add the Earl Sawyer card to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="survivors_interlude_powder">\n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add the Powder of Ibn-Ghazi
        card to his or her deck.</b></string>

    <string name="undimensioned_introduction">Your search of the village of Dunwich has uncovered a number of
        documents, journal entries, and esoteric theories. Reading through these materials leaves you exhausted and
        emotionally drained. Most of the content was written by a single source—a man named Seth Bishop. When you ask
        around town, you learn that Seth is a citizen of Dunwich. Along with several others, Seth had witnessed
        firsthand the devastation wrought by the events of “the Dunwich horror,” as Armitage had dubbed the incident.
        Curiously, since that time, very few people had seen Seth around town, and those who did claimed his eyes had
        been bloodshot and his face sweaty and pale.\n
    \nYou don’t doubt that somebody who has seen what Seth has seen would appear nervous or paranoid. But the more
        you read of his frantic and unhinged writings, the more you believe he is involved in recent events. His
        writings speak of having “gathered the remains” and of using arcane methods to “imbue the fathers’ essence”
        into other creatures, and eventually, into other people. The explanations and diagrams that follow are
        unfathomably complex and defy understanding.\n
    \nBefore you are able to find Seth and confront him, several men and women from the village approach you in a
        panic. “It’s back!” one of them wails. You recognize him as Curtis Whateley, of the undecayed branch.
        “Whatever it was that killed them Fryes, it’s back! Up and smashed the Bishops’ home like it were made o’
        paper!” Curtis and the other townsfolk are clamoring amongst themselves, raising their voices in a panic
        .</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_introduction_option_one">You try to calm down the townsfolk in order to learn more.</string>
    <string name="undimensoned_introduction_option_two">You try to warn the townsfolk and convince them to evacuate.</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_introduction_one">You aim to calm the townsfolk so they can explain to you what is
        going on. They inform you that there was a rumbling to the north, and when they went to investigate they
        found the Bishops’ farmhouse had been torn to shreds. A trail of heavy tracks led into nearby Cold Spring
        Glen. “You know what to do, right? You Arkham folk stopped that thing last time,” one of the townsfolk says.
        Curtis shakes his head and bites at his lip.\n
    \n“We couldn’t even see that hellish thing until the old professor sprayed that there powder on it,” He says. “To
        this day, I wish I hadn’t seen it at all…” Something must be done to stop the monster’s rampage. But, if the
        documents you found are true, there may be more than one such creature on the loose….</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_introduction_two">You warn the townsfolk that they are in grave danger, and urge them
        to flee Dunwich while they can. Several of them immediately heed your advice, remembering the terrible
        monstrosity that had previously endangered the town. Curtis drops to his knees in despair, sweating
        feverishly. “It’s that <b>thing</b> again, ain’t it? It’s come back fer us,” Curtis stutters. “I hope you’ve
        got some of that powder the old professor had last time. We couldn’t even see the damned thing until he
        sprayed it. To this day, I wish I hadn’t seen it at all…” Something must be done to stop the monster’s
        rampage. But, if the documents you found are true, there may be more than one such creature on the loose…
        .</string>

    <string name="doom_introduction_one">You awaken to the sound of screeching. Fearing the worst, you grab your
        equipment and head out into the streets of Dunwich. As soon as you step outside, you sense a foulness in the
        cold night air: an awful, pungent smell that can scarcely be described and a heaviness to the atmosphere that
        makes it difficult to breathe. The citizens of Dunwich have sealed their doors, and the town feels quiet and
        lonesome. In the distance, a faint glow emanates from a hilltop above the village. You know of this hill from
        both your interactions with Zebulon and Armitage’s records. It is called Sentinel Hill. The tales speak of
        satanic rites being performed there—rites in which great ritual-pyres light up the night sky while the ground
        rumbles furiously below.\n
    \nFlocks of whippoorwills perch on the rooftops of the village around you, watching ominously as you climb inside
        Zebulon’s old and beat-up truck. As you drive towards Sentinel Hill, more screeching fills the sky with an
        awful pitch that is painful to your ears. Everything you have read about and experienced in Dunwich has led
        to this. If the foul ritual Seth seeks to perform has anything to do with what Armitage and his colleagues
        prevented several months back, it involves the favor of an ancient creature—<b>Yog‑Sothoth</b>. Failing to
        stop this ritual may spell doom…not only Dunwich, but for the entire world.</string>
    <string name="doom_introduction_two">You awaken to the sound of screeching. Fearing the worst, you grab your
        equipment and head out into the streets of Dunwich. As soon as you step outside, you sense a foulness in the
        cold night air: an awful, pungent smell that can scarcely be described and a heaviness to the atmosphere that
        makes it difficult to breathe. The citizens of Dunwich have sealed their doors, and the town feels quiet and
        lonesome. In the distance, a faint glow emanates from a hilltop above the village. You know of this hill from
        both your interactions with Zebulon and Armitage’s records. It is called Sentinel Hill. The tales speak of
        satanic rites being performed there—rites in which great ritual-pyres light up the night sky while the ground
        rumbles furiously below.\n
    \nFlocks of whippoorwills perch on the rooftops of the village around you, watching ominously as you climb inside
        Zebulon’s old and beat-up truck. As you drive towards Sentinel Hill, more screeching fills the sky with an
        awful pitch that is painful to your ears. Everything you have read about and experienced in Dunwich has led
        to this. If the foul ritual Seth seeks to perform has anything to do with what Armitage and his colleagues
        prevented several months back, it involves the favor of an ancient creature—<b>Yog‑Sothoth</b>. Failing to
        stop this ritual may spell doom…not only Dunwich, but for the entire world.\n
        \nThe path leading up Sentinel Hill is narrow and too torn up for Zebulon’s
        truck, so you park at the base of the hill and prepare to make the rest of the trip on foot. Just then, you
        notice that you are not alone. Several men and women emerge from the woods behind you, brandishing firearms
        and lining you up in their sights. You raise your hands and brace for the worst. “Wait,” one of them says,
        raising his hand to the others. “I recognize you from the Clover Club.” He grins toothily and lowers his
        weapon. “Naomi sends her regards.”\n
    \nCurious, you ask what the gangsters are doing here. “Ms. O’Bannion had us investigate the attack on her
        fiancé’s club,” he explains. “Turns out there were some men in Arkham behind the whole thing. Some Bishop
        fellow and his lackeys. We tailed them all the way to this dump.” Before he can explain further, the
        all-too-familiar ratta-tat of a tommy gun echoes across the hill. “That’ll be Vinny. Come on, boys!” He
        beckons to the others to follow and runs up the hill. Shaking your head, you do the same. These mobsters
        don’t know what they’re getting into.</string>

    <string name="lost_introduction">Passing through the gate is unlike anything you’ve ever experienced. You feel
        your body twisting and distorting, churning through realities as the gate pulls you to its ultimate
        destination—a place beyond the scope of human imagination.\n
    \nSuddenly, all is quiet and the chaos of the journey is replaced with a sense of solitude and dread. You are in
        an unfathomable place, vast beyond your ability to reason and utterly alien besides. The landscape is surreal
        and strange, the architecture impossible. You are so far from home that home has become a threadbare dream
        you can barely recall. Even should you find a way out of this awful place, you may never be the same again
        .</string>

    <string name="dunwich_epilogue_one">Six months had passed, and life for Curtis Whateley was finally returning to
        normal. Since they’d hushed up the incident and the authorities kept their distance from these parts, Mr.
        Osborn had auctioned off the Ericks and Bishop families’ belongings. Joe took a few trinkets for himself, of
        course, but Curtis wanted nothing to do with it. Folk already didn’t trust him on account of his family’s
        sins, even though he’d been attending church on the regular and had stayed far away from anything resembling
        the arcane.\n
    \nEven so, Curtis could not shake a sense of foreboding. He’d seen the devastation that befell the Ericks,
        Bishop, and Frye homes. He’d even seen firsthand the creature the folks from Arkham had banished. Some days,
        his thoughts led him to Wilbur Whateley’s farm, where he would stand outside and stare for hours, too scared
        to enter, but too curious to leave. Maybe there was something in there that could make these terrible visions
        depart. Something that could give him strength enough to resist the nightmares. Curtis decided he would find
        it.</string>
    <string name="dunwich_epilogue_two">Gené knelt closer to the ground to examine the sign in the dirt. The shape of
        the sign was foreign to her, and the tracks that had led to it were unlike any she’d ever seen. Coupled with
        the report from the university…she wasn’t sure what to think. “Ms. Beauregard,” her assistant called out to
        her, “have you found something?”\n
    \nGené stood and turned to face the freshman who’d been assigned to her. He was a good kid and a bit callow, but
        a hard worker and eager to prove himself. “This place was supposed to be cordoned off,” Gené responded.
        “Nobody’s lived here for months. And yet, see for yourself: their primitive rites continue to this day.”\n
    \nThe student approached and joined Gené in examining the sign, flipping through the pages of his journal to
        reference its symbols. “What do you think it means?” he asked. She shook her head. Outsiders rarely traveled
        to Dunwich, and all the signposts leading to the village had been taken down. But these days, even the
        townsfolk who had called this place home had abandoned it.\n
    \n“I don’t know,” Gené admitted. “But somebody is here, and this isn’t the first sign we’ve seen like this.
        Stories say there’s an altar where the townsfolk would conduct pagan rituals atop that hill. Maybe we’ll find
        more up there.</string>


    <!--Scenario setup instructions-->
    <string name="extracurricular_sets">Extracurricular Activity, Sorcery, The Beyond, Bishop\'s Thralls,
        Whippoorwills, Ancient Evils, Locked Doors, and Agents of Yog-Sothoth.</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_locations">Put the Miskatonic Quad, Orne Library, Humanities Building,
        Student Union, Science Building, and Administration Building locations into play.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play at the Miskatonic Quad.\n</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_set_aside_one">Faculty Offices (The Night is Still Young), \"Jazz\" Mulligan,
        Alchemical Concoction, The Experiment, Professor Warren Rice, Dormitories, and Alchemy Labs.\n</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_set_aside_two">Faculty Offices (The Hour is Late), \"Jazz\" Mulligan,
        Alchemical Concoction, The Experiment, Professor Warren Rice, Dormitories, and Alchemy Labs.\n</string>

    <string name="house_sets">The House Always Wins, Bad Luck, Naomi\'s Crew, and Rats.</string>
    <string name="house_locations">Put the Clover Club Lounge, Clover Club Bar, Clover Club Cardroom, and La
        Bella Luna locations into play.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play in La Bella Luna.\n</string>
    <string name="house_set_aside">The Hideous Abominations and Striking Fear encounter sets.\n</string>
    <string name="house_set_aside_two">Darkened Hall, Peter Clover, Dr. Francis Morgan, and each copy of Back
        Hall Doorway.\n</string>
    <string name="house_additional">Put Clover Club Pit Boss into play in the Clover Club Lounge.</string>

    <string name="miskatonic_sets">The Miskatonic Museum, Bad Luck, Sorcery, The Beyond, Chilling Cold, and
        Locked Doors.</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_locations">Put one of the two Administration Office locations and one of the two
        Security Office locations into play at random. Remove the other versions from the game. Then, put the
        Museum Entrance and Museum Halls locations into play.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play at the Museum Entrance.\n</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_set_aside">Harold Walsted, Adam Lynch, The Necronomicon
        (<i>Olaus Wormius Translation</i>), and Shadow-spawned.\n</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_additional">Set the 6 "Exhibit Hall" locations aside as a separate "Exhibit Deck."
        To do this, perform the following:\n
    \nShuffle the Exhibit Hall (<i>Restricted Hall</i>) and 2 other random Exhibit Hall locations together to
        form the bottom 3 cards of the Exhibit Deck, unrevealed side faceup.\n
    \nThen, place the other 3 Exhibit Hall locations on top, in a random order. All 6 cards of the Exhibit Hall
    deck should be showing only the unrevealed side, so that the players do not know which Exhibit Hall is the
        Exhibit Hall (<i>Restricted Hall</i>).</string>

    <string name="essex_sets">The Essex County Express, The Beyond, Striking Fear, Ancient Evils, and Dark Cult.</string>
    <string name="essex_locations">Put one of the three Engine Car locations into play at random and remove the
    others from the game.\n
    \nPut six of the eight Train Car locations into play at random, in a straight line to the left of the
        Engine Car, and remove the others from the game.\n
    \nEach investigator beings play at the leftmost Train Car location.\n</string>
    <string name="essex_set_aside">All 4 copies of Across Space and Time.\n</string>
    <string name="essex_additional">Based on your difficulty level, add the following chaos token to the chaos
        bag, for the remainder of the campaign:\n
    \n\t\t<b>Easy:</b> -2\n
    \n\t\t<b>Standard:</b> -3\n
    \n\t\t<b>Hard:</b> -4\n
    \n\t\t<b>Expert:</b> -5</string>

    <string name="blood_sets">Blood on the Altar, Dunwich, Whippoorwills, Nightgaunts, and Ancient Evils.</string>
    <string name="blood_sets_two">Seeking vengeance, the gang from the Clover Club has followed you to Dunwich.
    Add the Naomi\'s Crew encounter set.</string>
    <string name="blood_locations">Put Village Commons into play.\n
    \nRemove one of the two copies of each other location from the game at random. Then, choose one of the six
        remaining locations at random, and remove it from the game as well. Put the remaining locations into
        play.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play in the Village Commons.\n</string>
    <string name="blood_set_aside">Silas Bishop, and Powder of Ibn-Ghazi.\n</string>
    <string name="blood_additional">Take The Hidden Chamber and Key to the Chamber cards, along with the top 3
        cards of the encounter deck. Shuffle them and randomly deal 1 card facedown underneath each location in
    play except Village Commons.\n\n</string>
    <string name="blood_additional_sacrifice_one">Form a facedown pile of "potential sacrifices", consisting of
    the</string>
    <string name="blood_additional_sacrifice_armitage">Dr. Henry Armitage,</string>
    <string name="blood_additional_sacrifice_rice">Professor Warren Rice,</string>
    <string name="blood_additional_sacrifice_morgan">Dr. Francis Morgan,</string>
    <string name="blood_additional_sacrifice_two">Zebulon Whateley, and Earl Sawyer cards.\n\n</string>
    <string name="blood_additional_two">Add 1 doom to agenda 1a.\n\n</string>

    <string name="undimensioned_sets">Undimensioned and Unseen, Whippoorwills, Beast-thralls, Dunwich, and Striking
        Fear.</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_locations">Put one of the two versions of the following locations into play at
        random: Dunwich Village, Cold Spring Glen, Blasted Heath, Ten-Acre Meadow, Devil\'s Hop Yard, and Whateley
        Ruins. Remove the other versions of each of those locations from the game.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play in Dunwich Village.\n</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_set_aside">Each copy of Esoteric Formula.\n</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_additional_brood_one">Set 2 copies of Brood of Yog‑Sothoth aside, out of play. Then,
        remove the final 3 copies of Brood of Yog‑Sothoth from the game.\n\n</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_additional_brood_two">Put 1 copy of Brood of Yog‑Sothoth into play in Cold Spring
        Glen, and set 2 copies of Brood of Yog‑Sothoth aside, out of play. Then, remove the final 2 copies of Brood
        of Yog‑Sothoth from the game.\n\n</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_additional_brood_three">Put 1 copy of Brood of Yog‑Sothoth into play in Cold Spring
        Glen, and set 3 copies of Brood of Yog‑Sothoth aside, out of play. Then, remove the final copy of Brood of
        Yog‑Sothoth from the game.\n\n</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_additional_brood_four">Put 1 copy of Brood of Yog‑Sothoth into play in Cold Spring
        Glen, put 1 copy of Brood of Yog‑Sothoth into play in Blasted Heath. Then, set the final 3 copies of Brood of
        Yog‑Sothoth aside, out of play.\n\n</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_additional_powder">The investigator with the Powder of Ibn-Ghazi in his or her deck
        may search his or her deck for it and put it into play.\n\n</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_additional">Each investigator searches the collection for a random basic Madness,
        Injury, or Pact weakness and adds it to his or her deck for the remainder of the campaign.\n\n</string>

    <string name="doom_sets">Where Doom Awaits, Beast-thralls, Sorcery, Bishop\’s Thralls, Striking Fear, Ancient
        Evils, and Chilling Cold.</string>
    <string name="doom_sets_two">Where Doom Awaits, Beast-thralls, Sorcery, Bishop\’s Thralls, Striking Fear, Ancient
        Evils, Chilling Cold, and Hideous Abominations.</string>
    <string name="doom_locations">Put Base of the Hill, Ascending Path, and Sentinel Peak into play.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play at Base of the Hill.\n</string>
    <string name="doom_set_aside">Remove 1 copy of Diverging Path from the game, at random. Set the other 3 copies of
        Diverging Path aside, out of play.\n
        \nRemove 1 copy of Altered Path from the game, at random. Set the other 3 copies of Altered Path aside, out of
        play.\n
        \nSet Seth Bishop aside, out of play.\n</string>
    <string name="doom_additional">Based on your difficulty level, add the following chaos token to the chaos
        bag, for the remainder of the campaign:\n
        \n\t\t<b>Easy:</b> -3\n
        \n\t\t<b>Standard:</b> -5\n
        \n\t\t<b>Hard:</b> -6\n
        \n\t\t<b>Expert:</b> -7\n</string>
    <string name="doom_additional_act_one">Use Act 2—Ascending the Hill (v. I).\n\n</string>
    <string name="doom_additional_act_two">Use Act 2—Ascending the Hill (v. II).\n\n</string>
    <string name="doom_additional_act_three">Use Act 2—Ascending the Hill (v. III).\n\n</string>
    <string name="doom_additional_obannion_one">The lead investigator gains a clue from the token bank.\n\n</string>
    <string name="doom_additional_obannion_two">The lead investigator gains two clues from the token bank
        .\n\n</string>
    <string name="doom_additional_doom">doom to agenda 1a.\n\n</string>
    <string name="doom_additional_bishop">Remnants of Silas Bishop\'s body have mutated and grown at Sentinel
        Hill. Put 1 \"Conglomeration of Spheres\" enemy into play at Ascending Path.\n\n</string>

    <string name="lost_sets">Lost in Time and Space, Sorcery, The Beyond, Hideous Abominations, and Agents of
        Yog-Sothoth.</string>
    <string name="lost_locations">Put Another Dimension into play.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play in Another Dimension.\n</string>
    <string name="lost_set_aside">The Edge of the Universe, Tear Through Time, and Yog-Sothoth.\n</string>


    <!--Scenario resolutions-->
    <string name="extracurricular_no_resolution">As you flee from the university, you hear screaming from the
        northern end of the campus. An ambulance passes you by, and you fear the worst. Hours later, you learn that a
        ‘rabid dog of some sort’ found its way into the university dormitories. The creature attacked the students
        inside and many were mauled or killed in the attack.\n
    \n<b>You are haunted by guilt. Add 1 Tablet chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="extracurricular_resolution_one">You find Professor Rice bound and gagged in the closet of his
        office. When you free him, he informs you that the strange men and women wandering around the campus had been
        stalking him for hours. They cornered him in his office and tied him up, although for what purpose, Rice
        isn’t sure. You inform him that Dr. Armitage sent you, and Rice looks relieved, although he suspects that Dr.
        Morgan might be in danger as well. Because the strangers on campus seem to have been targeting Professor
        Rice, you decide that the best course of action is to escort him away from the campus as quickly as possible.
        As you leave the university, you hear screaming from the northern end of the campus. An ambulance passes you
        by, and you fear the worst. Hours later, you learn that a ‘rabid dog of some sort’ found its way into the
        university dormitories. The creature attacked the students inside, and many were mauled or killed in the
        attack.\n
    \n<b>You are haunted by guilt. Add 1 Tablet chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the campaign.</b>\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Professor Warren Rice to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="extracurricular_resolution_two">You pull each of the dormitory’s fire alarms and usher the students
        out of the building’s north exit, hoping to make your way off campus. Many of the students are confused and
        exhausted, but you believe an attempt to explain the situation will do more harm than good. Minutes later, a
        terrible screech echoes across the campus, piercing and shrill. You tell the students to wait and head back
        to the dormitories to investigate. Oddly, you find no trace of the strange creature—a prospect that worries
        you more than it relieves you. You hurry to the faculty offices to find Professor Rice, but there is no sign
        of him anywhere.</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_resolution_three">After defeating the strange and terrifying creature from the
        Department of Alchemy, you rush to the faculty offices to find Professor Rice. By the time you get to his
        office, there is no sign of him anywhere.</string>
    <string name="extracurricular_resolution_four">You awaken hours later, exhausted and injured. You’re not sure
        what you saw, but the sight of it filled your mind with terror. From other survivors, you learn that a ‘rabid
        dog of some sort’ found its way into the university dormitories. The creature attacked the students inside,
        and many were mauled or killed in the attack.\n
    \n<b>You are haunted by guilt. Add 1 Tablet chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>

    <string name="house_no_resolution">You flee to the end of the block and pause to recover. Before you can catch
        your breath, the ground shakes with a thunderous crash. People emerge from their homes and storefronts to see
        what the ruckus is, and a crowd forms on the street. You head to the front of the crowd and are horrified to
        see the building from which you fled just minutes earlier reduced to rubble. There is no sign of Dr. Morgan
        anywhere.</string>
    <string name="house_resolution_one">You flee to the end of the block and pause to recover. Before you can catch
        your breath, the ground shakes with a thunderous crash. People emerge from their homes and storefronts to see
        what the ruckus is, and a crowd forms on the street. You head to the front of the crowd and are horrified to
        see the building from which you fled just minutes earlier reduced to rubble. There is no sign of Dr. Morgan
        anywhere.</string>
    <string name="house_resolution_two">“What in the world…?” Dr. Morgan finally breaks out of his daze as you make
        your way to safety. You ask him what he remembers, and he sputters and shakes his head. “It’s all a haze,” he
        explains, visibly exhausted. “I was having the run of my life! Perhaps I had one too many shots. But, those
        creatures—I haven’t seen anything like that since…” He trails off, and you can tell that his mind is racing.
        His eyes widen with realization and his face pales. “I may not be in the best shape, but I’ll help with your
        investigation. Whatever it takes.”\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Dr. Francis Morgan to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="house_resolution_three">Although you were unable to find Dr. Morgan in the club, the man you
        rescued is grateful for your help. He introduces himself as Peter Clover, the owner of the establishment
        you’d just left. Despite the situation, he maintains an air of quiet professionalism. As you make your way
        towards the street, a well-polished Chrysler B-70 rolls up to you, and a gorgeous woman with long brown hair
        and narrow eyes exits. She is flanked by dangerous-looking men who slip their hands under their suit jackets
        when they see you. “Peter,” she says with a sigh of relief, “Good, you’re okay. I heard there was trouble?”
        She turns and glares at you with deadly eyes. “Who are they?”\n
    \nMr. Clover dusts off his vest, unworried. “Naomi, my dear, these are friends of mine. They…” he clears his
        throat. “They escorted me off the premises,” he explains after a short pause. “They have earned our
        gratitude.” The woman crosses her arms and takes a moment to size you up before giving you a smirk.\n
    \n“Very well then. I must thank you for taking care of Peter. Run along now; we’ll handle things from here.” She
        nods to the goons flanking her and they walk past you toward the club’s rear entrance, pulling firearms out
        from underneath their coats. You’re not sure what ‘handling things’ means, but you’re pretty sure you don’t
        want to be here when the gunfire starts. You thank Naomi and Peter, and head off.</string>
    <string name="house_resolution_four">You are pulled from the debris by several firefighters, one of whom
        exclaims, “We’ve got a live one!” A few of them patch you up, and the cops ask you what happened. You’re
        certain they wouldn’t believe your story about horrible monstrosities demolishing the building from within.
        Unsure of what to say, you give a vague statement about not remembering much. “We’re bringing you to St.
        Mary’s,” one of the nurses says, pointing to a nearby ambulance. Knowing now how dire the situation is, you
        slip away while she is distracted by something else in the rubble…</string>

    <string name="miskatonic_no_resolution">Whatever the creature in the museum was, you had neither the will nor the
        tools to destroy it. It seems you must give up any hope of recovering the Necronomicon. Even so, there are
        others depending on you. Gathering your courage, you prepare for your next task.</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_resolution_one">As long as this translation of the Necronomicon exists, there will be
        sorcerers and other foul agents like Whateley seeking it. In the end, you know what must be done to protect
        humanity from the threats you’ve seen. You find a trash bin and fill it with books and documents, throwing
        the Necronomicon on top. It takes several matches to set the contents of the bin alight. The flames fill the
        room with heat and the creeping shadows retreat from its light. You watch the book burn for some time, its
        pages turning to ash. You can only hope you’ve made the right decision.</string>
    <string name="miskatonic_resolution_two">The Necronomicon is more than just a book; it is a tool. Within its
        pages is a wealth of information about the forces and creatures you have encountered. Knowing how useful it
        could be in your endeavors, how could you possibly bring yourself to destroy it? Besides, as long as you keep
        the book safely in your possession, you will still be foiling those who wish to use it for nefarious
        purposes.\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add The Necronomicon (Olaus Wormius Translation) to his or her deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>You have given in to the temptation of power. Add 1 Elder Thing chaos token to the chaos bag for the
            remainder of the campaign.</b></string>

    <string name="essex_no_resolution">Your experience beyond the gate is simultaneously terrifying and impossible
        to recall with clarity. A hypnotic
        spectacle of lights, otherworldly sensations, and altered geometry dances at the tattered edges of your mind.
        An unearthly voice from beyond rings in your ears, its significance an enigma. When you awaken, you find
        yourself in the woods, several miles from the Miskatonic River. Destroyed train cars surround you. They are
        crumpled as if from a severe impact; they are also decayed as if years of rust and squalor have claimed them.
        There is no sign of the other passengers.\n
        \nRattled, you begin walking alongside the train tracks, making your way towards Dunwich.\n
    \n<b>Each investigator who was defeated has acquired the Across Space and Time weakness and must add 1 copy of it
            to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="essex_resolution_one">You breathe a sigh of relief as the gate behind the train collapses
        harmlessly upon itself. The few passengers who survived the ordeal seem unable to comprehend what just
        happened. One passenger mentions “a pipe bursting in the rear car,” and that quickly becomes the explanation
        for the innocent and ignorant, those who either cannot or choose not to delve further into the mystery. You,
        on the other hand, know better… although in hindsight, you wish you didn’t.</string>
    <string name="essex_resolution_one_defeated"><b>Defeated investigators:</b>\n
    \nYour experience beyond the gate is simultaneously terrifying and impossible to recall with clarity. A hypnotic
        spectacle of lights, otherworldly sensations, and altered geometry dances at the tattered edges of your mind.
        An unearthly voice from beyond rings in your ears, its significance an enigma. When you awaken, you find
        yourself in the woods, several miles from the Miskatonic River. Destroyed train cars surround you. They are
        crumpled as if from a severe impact; they are also decayed as if years of rust and squalor have claimed them.
        There is no sign of the other passengers.\n
    \n<b>Each investigator who was defeated has acquired the Across Space and Time weakness and must add 1 copy of it
            to his or her deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>Surviving investigators:</b>\n
    \nYou breathe a sigh of relief as the gate behind the train collapses
        harmlessly upon itself. The few passengers who survived the ordeal seem unable to comprehend what just
        happened. One passenger mentions “a pipe bursting in the rear car,” and that quickly becomes the explanation
        for the innocent and ignorant, those who either cannot or choose not to delve further into the mystery. You,
        on the other hand, know better… although in hindsight, you wish you didn’t.</string>
    <string name="essex_resolution_two">Your experience beyond the gate is simultaneously terrifying and impossible
        to recall with clarity. A hypnotic
        spectacle of lights, otherworldly sensations, and altered geometry dances at the tattered edges of your mind.
        An unearthly voice from beyond rings in your ears, its significance an enigma. When you awaken, you find
        yourself in the woods, several miles from the Miskatonic River. Destroyed train cars surround you. They are
        crumpled as if from a severe impact; they are also decayed as if years of rust and squalor have claimed them.
        There is no sign of the other passengers.\n
        \nRattled, you begin walking alongside the train tracks, making your way towards Dunwich.\n
    \n<b>Each investigator who was defeated has acquired the Across Space and Time weakness and must add 1 copy of it
            to his or her deck.</b>\n
    \n<i><b>NOTE: Do not mark as \'Defeated\' any investigators defeated by Agenda 5b.</b></i></string>

    <string name="blood_no_resolution">The cries of the whippoorwills fade into the distance, and the town of Dunwich
        is filled with an eerie silence. All that can be heard is the dry whistle of the chill wind and the slow
        rustling of dead leaves. There is no sign of the missing townsfolk, nor will there be ever again.\n
    \n<b>If there were any potential sacrifices remaining at the end of the game, place them underneath the
            agenda deck.</b>\n
    \n<b>Each unique card that is underneath the agenda deck is removed from all players’ decks and can no longer be
            included in any players’ decks for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="blood_resolution_one">As you land the finishing blow, the creature’s body explodes into hundreds of
        squirming ropelike appendages, wriggling across the ground and climbing up the walls. You’re so startled that
        you aren’t fast enough to prevent them from escaping the room. Even so, whatever that creature was, you’re
        glad it’s now dead.\n
    \n<b>Each unique card that is underneath the agenda deck is removed from all players’ decks and can no longer be
            included in any players’ decks for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="blood_resolution_two">With the creature that once was Silas lashing out at you from its chains, you
        have little time to react. Knowing that the Necronomicon might have a spell or incantation that could subdue
        Silas, you fend off the abomination long enough to find a passage that can help. With no time to spare, you
        recite the Latin incantation, and find that the words come effortlessly to your tongue, as though recalled
        from an earlier memory. The creature’s body begins to shrink and melt away as the incantation builds, its
        cries terrifying and haunting. In the end, all that is left is the disfigured corpse of a man—Silas Bishop.
        You find a silver pendant emblazoned with an odd constellation tucked into his shirt. You take it with you,
        hoping to find a use for it.\n
    \n<b>Each unique card that is underneath the agenda deck is removed from all players’ decks and can no longer be
            included in any players’ decks for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="blood_resolution_three">With the creature that once was Silas lashing out at you from its chains,
        you have little time to react. Hoping there is something in the chamber you can use to your advantage, you
        fend off the abomination long enough to find a journal; many of its passages are written in Latin. It appears
        to be a handwritten excerpt from the Necronomicon, its purpose unknown. With no time to spare, you recite the
        incantation, stumbling over the words and feeling your throat tighten with each sentence. The creature’s body
        begins to shrink and melt away as the incantation continues, its cries terrifying and haunting. In the end,
        all that is left is a pile of wet and sticky ichor, and a rotten stench.\n
    \n<b>Each unique card that is underneath the agenda deck is removed from all players’ decks and can no longer be
            included in any players’ decks for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>

    <string name="undimensioned_no_resolution">You did all you could to stop the rampaging monsters, but there were
        more of them than you realized and you weren’t able to slay them all. Exhausted and terrified, you retreat to
        Zebulon’s home and hope to survive the night.</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_resolution_one">You did all you could to stop the rampaging monsters, but there were
        more of them than you realized and you weren’t able to slay them all. Exhausted and terrified, you retreat to
        Zebulon’s home and hope to survive the night.</string>
    <string name="undimensioned_resolution_two">After slaying what seems to be the last of the rampaging monsters you
        retreat to Zebulon’s home, exhausted and rattled by your experience.</string>

    <string name="doom_no_resolution">The sorcerers from Dunwich, seeking arcane power from beyond this realm, have
        accomplished what Wilbur and Old Whateley could not. Through blood sacrifice and indescribable experiments,
        the dark power the sorcerers sought is now within their reach. However, they will never get the chance to
        truly wield this power. In beseeching Wilbur’s father for knowledge, they have drawn the creature forth from
        its extradimensional realm. Yog-Sothoth emerges from the open rift above Sentinel Hill, blotting out the sky
        and enveloping the world. Now it has come to Earth, and it rules where humanity once tread.\n
    \n<b>The investigators lose the campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="doom_resolution_one">The poorly bound tome appears to be the written records of Old Whateley, the
        man who taught Wilbur the ancient secrets of sorcery. You find a passage describing a place outside of time
        and space, where worlds converge and Yog-Sothoth dwells. Only by reaching this nexus at the edge of reality
        can you unmake the tear that has split open the world. Feeling as if you may be going to your doom, you
        muster a final ounce of courage and step into the gate.</string>
    <string name="doom_resolution_two">The sorcerers from Dunwich, seeking arcane power from beyond this realm, have
        accomplished what Wilbur and Old Whateley could not. Through blood sacrifice and indescribable experiments,
        the dark power the sorcerers sought is now within their reach. However, they will never get the chance to
        truly wield this power. In beseeching Wilbur’s father for knowledge, they have drawn the creature forth from
        its extradimensional realm. Yog-Sothoth emerges from the open rift above Sentinel Hill, blotting out the sky
        and enveloping the world. Now it has come to Earth, and it rules where humanity once tread.\n
    \n<b>The investigators lose the campaign.</b></string>

    <string name="lost_no_resolution">Where did you come from? Why are you here? Are you dreaming, or is this place
        real? Now that you think about it, haven’t you been here before? Or perhaps you’ve been here all along. Now
        you remember. This is your real home. The path you now walk is but one ledge, with many more below. You only
        have to fall and you will be where you belong. One more step…\n
    \n<b>Each defeated investigator is killed.</b></string>
    <string name="lost_resolution_one">Lying on your back in a patch of wet grass, you find yourself staring
        longingly at the night sky. Somehow, you are once again atop Sentinel Hill, unable to recall exactly how you
        got here. You are mesmerized by the night sky. Seconds become minutes, and minutes become hours. Eventually,
        you are found and lifted to your feet by a group of Dunwich citizens. “What happened? What are ya doin’
        here?” they ask you, frightened but curious. You can’t seem to find the right words to describe the events
        that occurred beyond the gate…if they ever truly occurred. There doesn’t appear to be any trace of Seth
        Bishop, of the creatures you fought earlier, or of the phantasmal and otherworldly gate. But every time you
        sleep, you dream—and when you dream, it all comes rushing back.\n
    \n<b>The investigators win!</b></string>
    <string name="lost_resolution_one_defeated"><b>Defeated investigators:</b>\n
        \nWhere did you come from? Why are you here? Are you dreaming, or is this place
        real? Now that you think about it, haven’t you been here before? Or perhaps you’ve been here all along. Now
        you remember. This is your real home. The path you now walk is but one ledge, with many more below. You only
        have to fall and you will be where you belong. One more step…\n
    \n<b>Each defeated investigator is killed.</b>\n
        \n<b>Surviving investigators:</b>\n
    \nLying on your back in a patch of wet grass, you find yourself staring
        longingly at the night sky. Somehow, you are once again atop Sentinel Hill, unable to recall exactly how you
        got here. You are mesmerized by the night sky. Seconds become minutes, and minutes become hours. Eventually,
        you are found and lifted to your feet by a group of Dunwich citizens. “What happened? What are ya doin’
        here?” they ask you, frightened but curious. You can’t seem to find the right words to describe the events
        that occurred beyond the gate…if they ever truly occurred. There doesn’t appear to be any trace of Seth
        Bishop, of the creatures you fought earlier, or of the phantasmal and otherworldly gate. But every time you
        sleep, you dream—and when you dream, it all comes rushing back.\n
    \n<b>The investigators win!</b></string>
    <string name="lost_resolution_two">Where did you come from? Why are you here? Are you dreaming, or is this place
        real? Now that you think about it, haven’t you been here before? Or perhaps you’ve been here all along. Now
        you remember. This is your real home. The path you now walk is but one ledge, with many more below. You only
        have to fall and you will be where you belong. One more step…\n
    \n<b>Each defeated investigator is killed.</b>\n
    \nSeveral of the villagers from Dunwich heard the ruckus on Sentinel Hill and went to investigate. What they
        found there answered none of their questions.\n
    \n“What d’you think happened?” a frightened Curtis Whateley asks as they examine the hilltop. The other villagers
        shake their heads, unable to say. “Last thing I saw, the sky’d open’d up an’ there was a bright flash,” one
        of them says, looking up at the starry sky from the top of Sentinel Hill.\n
    \n“Those Arkham fellas ain’t nowhere to be seen,” Curtis adds, looking down at the cracked stone altar. “Not even
        of a hint of ‘em. Mr. Bishop and his pals, now, that’s a diff’rent story.” The young man motions toward
        several corpses on the ground.\n
    \n“Think we should get ahold of those coppers outta Aylesbury?”\n
    \n“Why, so they can laugh at us again?” Curtis spits. “They ain’t never gonna believe us ‘bout all this anyway.”
        He glances at the stone altar, fidgeting nervously. “Better t’ forget about the whole thing. C’mon, let’s
        bury the dead and get outta here.”\n
    \n<b>The investigators win…and are never seen or heard from again.</b></string>
    <string name="lost_resolution_three">The creature erupts in a cosmic fury of sound, color, and distorted space, hurling you back and away from it.
        You watch in horror as one of its arms tears through the fabric of the world, and its amorphous shape funnels
        through the rift, pulling the threads of the world along with it. You try to cling to something, but you are
        inexorably sucked into the rift. You feel as if your body is stretching and your mind is being crushed. Then,
        everything goes black.\n
    \n<b>Each investigator is killed.</b>\n
    \n<b>The investigators win…and are never seen or heard from again.</b></string>
    <string name="lost_resolution_three_defeated"><b>Defeated investigators:</b>\n
        \nWhere did you come from? Why are you here? Are you dreaming, or is this place
        real? Now that you think about it, haven’t you been here before? Or perhaps you’ve been here all along. Now
        you remember. This is your real home. The path you now walk is but one ledge, with many more below. You only
        have to fall and you will be where you belong. One more step…\n
        \n<b>Surviving investigators:</b>\n
    \nThe creature erupts in a cosmic fury of sound, color, and distorted space, hurling you back and away from it.
        You watch in horror as one of its arms tears through the fabric of the world, and its amorphous shape funnels
        through the rift, pulling the threads of the world along with it. You try to cling to something, but you are
        inexorably sucked into the rift. You feel as if your body is stretching and your mind is being crushed. Then,
        everything goes black.\n
    \n<b>Each investigator is killed.</b>\n
    \n<b>The investigators win…and are never seen or heard from again.</b></string>
    <string name="lost_resolution_four">Where did you come from? Why are you here? Are you dreaming, or is this place
        real? Now that you think about it, haven’t you been here before? Or perhaps you’ve been here all along. Now
        you remember. This is your real home. The path you now walk is but one ledge, with many more below. You only
        have to fall and you will be where you belong. One more step…\n
    \n<b>Each defeated investigator is killed.</b>\n
    \nThe sorcerers from Dunwich, seeking arcane power from beyond this realm, have accomplished what Wilbur and Old
        Whateley could not. Through blood sacrifice and indescribable experiments, the dark power the sorcerers
        sought is now within their reach. However, they will never get the chance to truly wield this power. In
        beseeching Wilbur’s father for knowledge, they have drawn the creature forth from its extradimensional realm.
        Yog-Sothoth emerges from the open rift above Sentinel Hill, blotting out the sky and enveloping the world.
        Now it has come to Earth, and it rules where humanity once tread.\n
    \n<b>Each surviving investigator is driven insane.</b>\n
    \n<b>The investigators lose.</b></string>

</resources>