<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="forgotten_campaign">The Forgotten Age</string>
    <string name="forgotten_scenario_one">Scenario 1: The Untamed Wilds</string>
    <string name="forgotten_scenario_two">Scenario 2: The Doom of Eztli</string>
    <string name="forgotten_scenario_three">Scenario 3: Threads of Fate</string>
    <string name="forgotten_scenario_four">Scenario 4: The Boundary Beyond</string>
    <string name="forgotten_scenario_five">Scenario 5: Heart of the Elders</string>
    <string name="forgotten_scenario_six">Scenario 6: The City of Archives</string>
    <string name="forgotten_scenario_seven">Scenario 7: The Depths of Yoth</string>
    <string name="forgotten_scenario_eight">Scenario 8: Shattered Aeons</string>
    <string name="forgotten_interlude_one">Interlude 1: Restless Nights</string>
    <string name="forgotten_interlude_two">Interlude 2: Expedition\'s End</string>
    <string name="forgotten_interlude_three">Interlude 3: The Jungle Beckons</string>
    <string name="forgotten_interlude_four">Interlude 4: Those Held Captive</string>
    <string name="forgotten_interlude_five">Interlude 5: The Darkness</string>
    <string name="forgotten_epilogue">Epilogue</string>


    <!--Miscellaneous-->
    <string name="vengeance_counter">Vengeance: </string>
    <string name="advanced_act_three">Advanced to Act 3</string>
    <string name="untamed_ichtaca_one">Scenario ended on Act 1 or 2</string>
    <string name="untamed_ichtaca_two">You fought with Ichtaca</string>
    <string name="untamed_ichtaca_three">Ichtaca is leading the way</string>
    <string name="harbinger">Harbinger of Valusia is still in play or set aside</string>
    <string name="harbinger_damage">Damage on the Harbinger of Valusia: </string>
    <string name="eztli_resolution_three_option_one">“We can’t stop now—we have to go back inside!”</string>
    <string name="eztli_resolution_three_option_two">“It’s too dangerous. This place must be destroyed.”</string>


    <!--Supplies-->
    <string name="supplies">Supplies</string>
    <string name="choose_supplies">Choose Supplies</string>
    <string name="points_available">pts available</string>
    <string name="not_enough_points">You do not have enough supply points available.</string>
    <string name="provisions_description">Provisions (1pt):
        <i>Food and water for one person. A must-have for any journey.</i></string>
    <string name="medicine_description">Medicine (2pts): <i>To stave off disease, infection, or venom.</i></string>
    <string name="rope_description">Rope (3pts):
        <i>Several long coils of strong rope. Vital for climbing and spelunking.</i></string>
    <string name="blanket_description">Blanket (2pts): <i>For warmth at night.</i></string>
    <string name="canteen_description">Canteen (2pts): <i>Can be refilled at streams and rivers.</i></string>
    <string name="torches_description">Torches (3pts): <i>Can light up dark areas, or set sconces alight.</i></string>
    <string name="compass_description">Compass (2pts): <i>Can guide you when you are hopelessly lost.</i></string>
    <string name="map_description">Map (3pts): <i>Unmarked for now, but with time, you may be able to map out your
        surroundings.</i></string>
    <string name="binoculars_description">Binoculars (2pts): <i>To help you see faraway places.</i></string>
    <string name="chalk_description">Chalk (2pts): <i>For writing on rough stone surfaces.</i></string>
    <string name="pendant_description">Pendant (1pt):
        <i>Useless, but fond memories bring comfort to travelers far from home.</i></string>
    <string name="provisions_choose">Provisions (1pt):</string>
    <string name="medicine_choose">Medicine (2pts):</string>
    <string name="rope_choose">Rope (3pts)</string>
    <string name="blanket_choose">Blanket (2pts)</string>
    <string name="canteen_choose">Canteen (2pts)</string>
    <string name="torches_choose">Torches (3pts)</string>
    <string name="compass_choose">Compass (2pts)</string>
    <string name="map_choose">Map (3pts)</string>
    <string name="binoculars_choose">Binoculars (2pts)</string>
    <string name="chalk_choose">Chalk (2pts)</string>
    <string name="pendant_choose">Pendant (1pt)</string>
    <string name="provisions">Provisions</string>
    <string name="medicine">Medicine</string>
    <string name="rope">Rope</string>
    <string name="blanket">Blanket</string>
    <string name="canteen">Canteen</string>
    <string name="torches">Torches</string>
    <string name="compass">Compass</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>
    <string name="binoculars">Binoculars</string>
    <string name="chalk">Chalk</string>
    <string name="pendant">Pendant</string>
    <string name="no_supplies">No supplies</string>


    <!--Campaign log-->
    <string name="yigs_fury">Yig’s Fury: </string>
    <string name="forced_wait">The investigators were forced to wait for additional supplies.\n\n</string>
    <string name="cleared_path">The investigators cleared a path to the Eztli ruins.\n\n</string>
    <string name="ichtaca_observed">Ichtaca observed your progress with keen interest.\n\n</string>
    <string name="ichtaca_trust">The investigators have earned Ichtaca’s trust.\n\n</string>
    <string name="ichtaca_wary">Ichtaca is wary of the investigators.\n\n</string>
    <string name="alejandro_remained">Alejandro chose to remain at camp.\n\n</string>
    <string name="alejandro_followed">Alejandro followed the investigators into the ruins.\n\n</string>
    <string name="investigators_recovered_relic">The investigators recovered the Relic of Ages.\n\n</string>
    <string name="alejandro_recovered_relic">Alejandro recovered the Relic of Ages.\n\n</string>
    <string name="harbinger_alive">The Harbinger is still alive.</string>
    <string name="custody_alejandro">The investigators gave custody of the relic to Alejandro.\n\nThe investigators
        have earned Alejandro’s trust.\n\n</string>
    <string name="custody_harlan">The investigators gave custody of the relic to Harlan Earnstone.\n\nAlejandro is
        continuing his research on his own.\n\n</string>

    <!--Edit log-->
    <string name="yigs_fury_heading">Yig’s Fury</string>
    <string name="ruins_heading">Eztli Ruins</string>
    <string name="ichtaca_heading">Ichtaca</string>
    <string name="alejandro_heading">Alejandro</string>
    <string name="harbinger_heading">Harbinger of Valusia</string>
    <string name="relic_heading">Relic of Ages</string>
    <string name="custody_heading">Custody of the Relic</string>

    <!--Chaos bag-->
    <string name="untamed_skull_one">–X. X is the number of vengeance points in the victory display.</string>
    <string name="untamed_skull_two">–X. X is 1 higher than the number of vengeance points in the victory display.</string>
    <string name="untamed_cultist_one">–X. X is the number of locations in play (max 5).</string>
    <string name="untamed_cultist_two">–X. X is the number of locations in play.</string>
    <string name="untamed_tablet_one">–X. X is the number of cards in the exploration deck (max 5).</string>
    <string name="untamed_tablet_two">–X. X is the number of cards in the exploration deck (min 3).</string>
    <string name="untamed_thing_one">–2. If you are poisoned, this test automatically fails instead.</string>
    <string name="untamed_thing_two">–3. If you are poisoned, this test automatically fails instead. If you are not
        poisoned and you fail, put a set-aside Poisoned weakness into play in your threat area.</string>

    <string name="eztli_skull_one">–1 (–3 instead if there is doom on your location).</string>
    <string name="eztli_skull_two">–2 (–4 instead if there is doom on your location).</string>
    <string name="eztli_cultist_tablet_one">–X. X is the number of locations with doom on them.</string>
    <string name="eztli_cultist_tablet_two">–X. X is the total amount of doom on locations in play.</string>
    <string name="eztli_thing_one">Reveal another chaos token. If you fail, place 1 doom on your location.</string>
    <string name="eztli_thing_two">Reveal another chaos token. Place 1 doom on your location.</string>


    <!--Campaign introduction-->
    <string name="forgotten_introduction"><b>Prologue</b>\n
    \nTuesday, June 2nd, 1925\n
    \nThere will be no rest for us this summer, it seems.\n
    \nToday I met with Harlan Earnstone, a historical theorist at Miskatonic University and an old friend of mine.
        He’d said he had a job offer for me, but frankly, I didn’t know what to expect.\n
    \nHarlan introduced me to an associate of his: Alejandro Vela, a distinguished historian from across the southern
        border. Mr. Vela is a graduate of a prestigious university in Mexico City, and has spent many years
        researching the Aztec Empire. He claims that he has found evidence regarding the existence of an unheard-of
        Aztec city-state called Eztli. His strange and unprecedented findings were not accepted by the university,
        and he’s become a pariah among his peers.\n
    \nAlejandro came to Arkham to seek funding for an expedition into the rainforests of southern Mexico, where he
        believes that the ruins of the Eztli altepetl lie undiscovered. His description of this city-state’s origins
        defies modern understanding of Mesoamerican history. Despite this—or, knowing my old friend, because of
        this—Harlan is enthralled by Alejandro’s discoveries. Miskatonic University has agreed to fund the expedition
        (albeit meagerly), and Harlan wants me to go along.\n
    \nThe way I see it, there’s a good chance we’re looking for something that doesn’t even exist. But if there’s
        even a slight chance these Eztli people existed, the historical significance would be profound. We debated
        the issue for some time, but in the end, we accepted Alejandro’s offer. Preparations are underway, and we
        should be setting off by the end of the month. With any luck, we’ll have this journal filled with all manner
        of interesting discoveries. If not, perhaps it’ll be a nice wedge to place beneath Harlan’s lopsided desk.</string>


    <!--Interludes-->
    <string name="restless_blanket_one">The following investigators have blankets and get a restful sleep:\n\n</string>
    <string name="restless_blanket_two">\nThey read:</string>
    <string name="restless_restful_sleep">Mercifully, I was able to sleep through each night. However, while my body
        rested, my mind was plagued by nightmares. A cavern like a gaping maw, bathed in dim red light…the walls
        slithering with the glimmering scales of a hundred vipers…it might have been better had I not slept at all.\n</string>
    <string name="restless_no_blanket_one">The following investigators do not have blankets and are tossing and
    turning:\n\n</string>
    <string name="restless_no_blanket_two">\nThey read:</string>
    <string name="restless_tossing_turning">Those nights in the jungle, I barely slept. A strange fog rolled through
        the camp each night, plunging the area in an intense and peculiar cold. My bedroll offered some protection
        against the elements, but we hadn’t been prepared for this unnatural weather. Flies and mosquitoes buzzed in
        my ears every time I began to drift off. Even when I finally slept, I would soon be startled awake by the
        crawling of an insect or lizard across my face. I wager I’ll get very little sleep on this journey…</string>
    <string name="restless_no_blanket_option_one">Take a physical trauma</string>
    <string name="restless_no_blanket_option_two">Take a mental trauma</string>

    <string name="restless_not_low">The investigators have enough provisions.</string>
    <string name="restless_low_one">The investigators do not have enough provisions and are low on rations.
        Choose</string>
    <string name="restless_low_two_single_investigator">investigator to read:\n</string>
    <string name="restless_low_two_multiple_investigator">investigators to read:\n</string>
    <string name="restless_low">We thought we’d brought enough food and water for everybody, but the journey had
        taken its toll on our supplies. When the sun rose and it came time to eat, we discovered we were already
        running out of provisions.\n</string>
    <string name="restless_low_effect">Each of those investigators begins the next scenario with 3 fewer resources.</string>

    <string name="restless_choose_lookout">The lead investigator must choose one investigator to be the group’s
        lookout.</string>
    <string name="restless_binoculars"> (has binoculars)</string>
    <string name="restless_lookout_reads">\nThat investigator reads:</string>
    <string name="restless_shapes_trees">Most of the nights passed without incident, but on this night, I was
        startled by the rustling of tree branches along the southern border of our camp’s clearing. Despite the
        darkness, I was able to use my binoculars to see shapes moving in the trees. The shapes appeared human,
        but…why? Why do they only watch us from afar? What is their purpose?</string>
    <string name="restless_eyes_dark">Each night, I was watched. I didn’t just feel watched: I saw the eyes peering
        out from the inky darkness that surrounded our camp. They knew we were there. The yellow eyes watched me,
        alert, my weapons drawn, ready to defend the camp if the need arose. Our eyes met, and a darkness seized my
        heart.</string>

    <string name="restless_poison_one_single_investigator">investigator may use medicine and remove a Poisoned weakness
        from their deck.</string>
    <string name="restless_poison_one_multiple_investigators">investigators may use medicine and remove a Poisoned
        weakness from their deck.</string>
    <string name="restless_poison_counter">Medicine used</string>
    <string name="restless_poisoned_heading">Investigators still poisoned</string>
    <string name="restless_poison_two">The investigators have no medicine to cure their poison.</string>
    <string name="restless_poison_three">\nEach investigator who still has a Poisoned weakness in their deck
        reads:</string>
    <string name="restless_poison_spreads">As the days went by, the poison continued to spread through my body. By
        the second night, my skin was drenched in sweat. I started having difficutly breathing, and I began every
        morning by retching up most of the previous night’s dinner.</string>

    <string name="expeditions_end_one">Friday, July 17th, 1925\n
    \nWe have finally made it back to Arkham, our expedition a “success.” Alejandro is excited to report his findings
        to the university. How he maintains his starry-eyed idealism after the hell we went through in the jungle is
        beyond me. His attention is fixated on the strange relic that we discovered in the ruins. I wish we knew a
        little more about the artifact’s origins. It unsettles me greatly. It hums at all times and pulses with an
        otherworldly energy I can scarcely describe. As we traveled home with the artifact in tow, our nights were
        plagued by bizarre nightmares: dreams of other worlds and civilizations.\n
    \nAlejandro wants to bring the relic to the Miskatonic Museum, to put on display along with the other Eztli
        artifacts we discovered. My feelings are mixed. At the museum, it will receive proper care, and historians
        will be able to study it and perhaps even discern its purpose. However, I fear that the relic may be too
        dangerous for the public. After all, we still have no idea what the damned thing even is. Alejandro would
        hate it, but perhaps it would be better to keep the relic somewhere safe, where Harlan and I can study it in
        private. I’ll have to decide tonight; after tomorrow, there won’t be time to change my mind…</string>
    <string name="expeditions_end_two">Sunday, July 19th, 1925\n
    \nI’ve decided to give custody of the relic to Alejandro. This entire expedition was based on his research, after
        all—he should be the one to study it. If anyone can discover the relic’s secrets, it’s him.\n
    \nThe relic is to be the centerpiece of a new exhibit at the museum. Alejandro has already written extensively
        about our discoveries, but his work has only just begun. Many mysteries about our expedition remain. How have
        the Eztli people remained undiscovered for so long? Why did they appear to be guarding the jungle, and from
        what? Who really built the temple ruins we explored? I have no doubt Alejandro will uncover the answers to
        these questions, given enough time.\n
    \nAs for me, my role in this endeavor has ended. However, I have yet to relax. My thoughts are constantly in the
        jungle—serpentine figures in the shadows, obsidian arrows embedded in skeletal bodies, malformed voices
        shrieking in the cavernous depths. When I walk through the streets, I find myself drawn toward the museum
        without realizing it, as though possessed to see the relic once again. There is a nagging sensation in the
        back of my mind, as though we have forgotten something important. What must I do to rid myself of—\n
    \n(The journal entry ends abruptly.)\n
        \n<b>If it is not already in an investigator’s deck, any one investigator may choose to add Alejandro Vela to
            his or her deck.</b>\n
        \n<b>Add 1 Tablet chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the campaign.</b>\n
    \nYou drop your pen as a loud knocking at the door startles you, and you jump to your feet. It is almost 2:30 in
        the morning. Who could possibly be at your door at this hour? Your thoughts wander again to the jungle, and
        you are faced with a vision of serpent-creatures attacking you in your own home. Shuddering, you find a
        weapon and approach the front door carefully, ready to strike if need be. You take a long breath and open the
        door.\n
    \nOn the other side is a familiar woman with brown skin, long brown hair, and piercing yellow eyes set in a hard
        glare. Though her attire has changed, you recognize her instantly as Ichtaca, the Eztli warrior you
        encountered in the rainforest. Wearing a long coat and a Bollman hat, she is visibly uncomfortable in her
        shoes. Her jaw is set in anger. You are about to raise your weapon in defense when she lets out a heavy sigh
        and walks slowly over the threshold of your home, shutting your front door behind her. “Whatever you did, you
        have to reverse it,” she intones darkly. “Or we will <i>all</i> cease to exist.”</string>
    <string name="expeditions_end_three">Sunday, July 19th, 1925\n
    \nI’ve decided to keep the relic hidden for now. Alejandro is not happy with my decision, but until we know what
        the orb is capable of, it’s important that it stay somewhere safe, where it won’t endanger others. Harlan
        agrees with me, and has offered to take custody of the relic and keep it in his private office. There, we can
        study the artifact in secret.\n
    \nAlejandro is staying in Arkham for the time being, recording his notes about the expedition and helping the
        museum put together an exhibit displaying our other, less dangerous discoveries. As for me, I hope to find
        answers to other mysteries: How have the Eztli people remained undiscovered for so long? Why did they appear
        to be guarding the jungle, and from what? Who really built the temple ruins we explored?\n
    \nMy thoughts are constantly in the jungle—serpentine figures in the shadows, obsidian arrows embedded in
        skeletal bodies, malformed voices shrieking in the cavernous depths. Each time I leave Harlan’s office, I
        find myself longing to head back and gaze upon the relic once more. There is a nagging sensation in the back
        of my mind, as though we have forgotten something important. What must I do to rid myself of—\n
    \n(The journal entry ends abruptly.)\n
        \n<b>If Alejandro Vela is currently in an investigator’s deck, remove him from that investigator’s deck.</b>\n
    \nYou drop your pen as a loud knocking at the door startles you, and you jump to your feet. It is almost 2:30 in
        the morning. Who could possibly be at your door at this hour? Your thoughts wander again to the jungle, and
        you are faced with a vision of serpent-creatures attacking you in your own home. Shuddering, you find a
        weapon and approach the front door carefully, ready to strike if need be. You take a long breath and open the
        door.\n
    \nOn the other side is a familiar woman with brown skin, long brown hair, and piercing yellow eyes set in a hard
        glare. Though her attire has changed, you recognize her instantly as Ichtaca, the Eztli warrior you
        encountered in the rainforest. Wearing a long coat and a Bollman hat, she is visibly uncomfortable in her
        shoes. Her jaw is set in anger. You are about to raise your weapon in defense when she lets out a heavy sigh
        and walks slowly over the threshold of your home, shutting your front door behind her. “Whatever you did, you
        have to reverse it,” she intones darkly. “Or we will <i>all</i> cease to exist.”</string>
    <string name="expeditions_end_five">Harlan Earnstone paces across your living room, dabbing his wrinkled forehead
        with his handkerchief. “It’s my fault. I should never have encouraged them to go on that dreadful
        expedition.” Though your paths have only crossed a few times before, Mr. Earnstone has become a valuable
        contact of yours within Miskatonic University. When the University’s latest expedition returned with only a
        few survivors and a handful of strange, archaic artifacts, he came to you for advice.\n
    \n“I know, I know. I should at least take solace in the fact that the expedition was successful, despite its
        heavy losses. Alejandro was right all along. The Eztli people are real. And yet…I am concerned about some of
        these findings.” Harlan pulls a small leather-bound journal from his suitcase and hands it to you. “Before
        the expedition leader’s tragic death, the leader recorded many of the group’s discoveries in this journal.
        One of the surviving members of the expedition managed to grab it from the camp before fleeing the jungle. I
        think if you read these entries, you’ll understand what I mean. The things they experienced, the creatures
        they encountered…” Harlan shudders and adjusts his glasses with too-shaky hands. “I am concerned not only for
        Alejandro, but for all of us. Read this journal, and if you can, please keep an eye on my colleague.” You
        agree to help, but his worry does not fade. “I only hope that I am not damning you to a similar fate by
        asking for your aid.”\n
    \nYou spend the remainder of that night studying the expedition journal, your mind swimming with thoughts of
        strange serpent-creatures and Aztec warriors. Long after Harlan has left, a loud knocking at the door
        startles you, and you jump to your feet. It is almost 2:30 in the morning. Who could possibly be at your door
        at this hour? You open the front door warily. On the other side is a woman with brown skin, long brown hair,
        and piercing yellow eyes set in a hard glare. She wears a long coat and a Bollman-style hat, visibly
        uncomfortable in her shoes. Her jaw is set in anger. A sudden flash of insight crosses your mind, and you
        realize at once who she must be. After all, you’ve read and re-read the journal’s description of Ichtaca, the
        Eztli warrior. She lets out a heavy sigh and walks slowly over the threshold of your home, shutting your
        front door behind her. “Whatever they did, you have to reverse it,” she intones darkly. “Or we will <i>all
        </i> cease to exist.”</string>
    <string name="expeditions_end_option_one">It belongs in a museum. Alejandro and the museum staff will be able to
        study it and learn more about its purpose.</string>
    <string name="expeditions_end_option_two">It is too dangerous to be on display. We should keep it hidden and safe
        until we know more about it.</string>


    <!--Scenario introductions-->
    <string name="untamed_introduction">Sunday, June 28th, 1925\n
    \nIt’s been a hell of a day. We’ve just set up camp along the northern border of the rainforest where Alejandro
        believes the Eztli once dwelled. The jungle here is dense and untamed. The sky hides above the tree cover,
        but I can tell from the crisp breeze that storm clouds are brewing overhead.\n
    \nThe dangers of our expedition have been explained to us many times. We are hundreds of miles away from any sign
        of civilization. Nobody in modern times has yet to pierce the heart of these wilds. Until now, nobody has had
        reason to try. After all, it wouldn’t make sense to find Aztec ruins in this region of Mexico. And yet, here
        we are: looking for ruins that may not exist in a place where, by all accounts, they should not.\n
    \nAlready one of our surveyors has fallen ill, and another has been bitten by a viper. I’m starting to think the
        rainforest doesn’t want us here. If this luck persists, ours will be the shortest expedition in Miskatonic
        University’s history. Tonight, we rest. Tomorrow, we venture into uncharted wilds.</string>

    <string name="eztli_introduction_one">Wednesday, July 8th, 1925\n
    \nOur runners, José and Maria, returned several days later. They were fully stocked with food, water, aspirin,
        and weapons. I am curious how deep Alejandro’s connections are in Mexico. For an outcast historian, he was
        able to secure guns and ammunition faster than I had anticipated. But perhaps it is better if he keeps his
        sources undisclosed.\n
    \nWe ventured once more into the jungle. This time, we were prepared. We had learned from our previous excursion,
        and we made our way across the river canyon, venturing deeper south than we had dared before. Eventually we
        reached the ruins Alejandro sought, and soon we will enter what Alejandro believes is the main temple.
        Strangely, the serpent creatures we encountered earlier didn’t attack in force as we had feared. Could they
        have fled? Or are they simply lying in wait, preparing to ambush while we sleep at night?</string>
    <string name="eztli_introduction_two">Friday, July 3rd, 1925\n
    \nWe spent most of yesterday moving our camp to the edge of the ruins. With the serpentine creatures still
        guarding the region, we have decided that a small party will have the best chance of slipping into the main
        temple unnoticed. I told Maria, the expedition’s naturalist, to take one of the trucks and wait beyond the
        northern edge of the rainforest. Our cartographer, José, is guarding the camp until we return. We’re on our
        own, but at least we’ve cleared an escape route in the event things go sour…</string>

    <string name="threads_introduction_one">The night passes with Ichtaca resting in your living room. You get no
        sleep for the remainder of the night, your thoughts drifting between concern and disbelief. Her story is
        preposterous, but you feel compelled to believe it nonetheless. You’ve known that the relic from the Eztli
        ruins had some deeper purpose ever since you first laid eyes on it. When you emerge from your bedroom the
        next morning, your uninvited guest is sitting at your dining-room table, arms crossed tightly across her
        chest. Her piercing eyes trace your every move like a bird watching its prey. No pleasantries are exchanged.
        “Where is the relic now?” Ichtaca asks impatiently. “Where have you brought it?” You explain that it is safe,
        in good hands. She shakes her head, her knuckles white with frustration. “I assure you it is not.”\n
    \nSetting aside your many questions for the time being, you call your contact at the Miskatonic University
        Museum. Despite the early hour, Dr. Horowitz should be at her office preparing for the long day ahead of her.
        The operator connects you after a short delay. Elli gives you an unusually curt greeting, her voice cracking
        and unsteady. As soon as you ask about the relic, she scoffs. “Not you, too! Mr. Walsted is practically
        knocking down my office door, and two reporters have been harassing me all morning!”\n
    \nYou ask her what the trouble is, and she lets out a long sigh. “The relic is <i>missing</i>,” she explains.
        “None of the security guards knows what happened. One minute it was in its display case; the next it was
        gone. And before you ask, no, Mr. Vela is nowhere to be found.” Suddenly she is yelling to another party,
        “One moment please! I am on the telephone!” She apologizes to you tersely and hangs up a moment later.\n
    \nSure enough, Alejandro is not answering his telephone, and none of his other associates have seen him since
        yesterday. “Believe me now?” Ichtaca asks, rising to her feet and gathering her things. “We’ve wasted enough
        time. Find the relic and meet me back here tonight. <i>Don’t</i> follow me.”</string>
    <string name="threads_introduction_two">The night passes with Ichtaca resting in your living room. You get no
        sleep for the remainder of the night, your thoughts drifting between concern and disbelief. Her story is
        preposterous, but you feel compelled to believe it nonetheless. You’ve known that the relic from the Eztli
        ruins had some deeper purpose ever since you first laid eyes on it. When you emerge from your bedroom the
        next morning, your uninvited guest is sitting at your dining-room table, arms crossed tightly across her
        chest. Her piercing eyes trace your every move like a bird watching its prey. No pleasantries are exchanged.
        “Where is the relic now?” Ichtaca asks impatiently. “Where have you brought it?” You explain that it is safe,
        in good hands. She shakes her head, her knuckles white with frustration. “I assure you it is not.”\n
    \nSetting aside your many questions for the time being, you call Harlan’s office at the university. Though the
        sun is barely peeking over the horizon, you’ve always known him to be an early riser. The operator connects
        you after a short delay. Harlan’s voice is shaky and rough. He cuts you off as soon as you ask about the
        relic. “Don’t!” he barks. “They’re listening. They know I am keeping it here. They have already taken
        Alejandro.” You try to calm him down so you can ask him what he means, but he cuts the conversation short. “I
        have to go. They are here!—” The line goes dead.\n
    \nSure enough, Alejandro is not answering his telephone, and none of his other associates have seen him since
        yesterday. “Believe me now?” Ichtaca asks, rising to her feet and gathering her things. “We’ve wasted enough
        time. Find the relic and meet me back here tonight. <i>Don’t</i> follow me.”</string>
    <string name="threads_introduction_option_one">“You’re not going anywhere until you tell me what is going on.”</string>
    <string name="threads_introduction_option_two">“Have it your way.”</string>
    <string name="threads_introduction_three">Ichtaca grits her teeth and pauses. You expect her to refuse and leave
        without answering your questions, but surprisingly, she relents. According to Ichtaca, her people have spent
        ages protecting the relic from interlopers who would use it for nefarious purposes. She speaks cryptically,
        in half-riddles and tall tales, although she refuses to explain where her people come from and how they have
        remained hidden for so long. When pressed about the relic, all she says is that it controls the flow of time,
        and that it must not be tampered with.\n
    \n“It must return to its rightful place,” she explains. Her gaze is relentless, unwavering. “Do you understand?
        It cannot fall into the wrong hands. If you help me recover it, I will aid you in return. Just promise me you
        <i>will not use it</i>.”\n
    \n<b>Remember that “you listened to Ichtaca’s tale.”</b>\n
    \n<b>Add 1 Cultist chaos token to the chaos bag for the remainder of the campaign.</b></string>
    <string name="threads_introduction_four">Ichtaca strings her ornately decorated bow with frightening speed and
        slams your door on her way out.\n
    \n<b>Remember that “Ichtaca left without you.”</b></string>
    <string name="threads_introduction_five">Ichtaca strings her ornately decorated bow with frightening speed and
        slams your door on her way out.\n
    \n<b>Remember that “Ichtaca left without you.”</b>\n
    \nOnce Ichtaca has left, you consider her words carefully and recall the events that have led to this point. You
        did not trust Alejandro with the Eztli relic, and you let Ichtaca leave without questioning her. Are you just
        being paranoid?…</string>
    <string name="threads_introduction_option_three">“We should be wary of them.”</string>
    <string name="threads_introduction_option_four">“Maybe I should listen to them after all…”</string>
    <string name="threads_introduction_six"><b>Remove all Cultist and Tablet chaos tokens from the chaos bag and
        replace them with 1 Elder Thing token.</b>\n
    \n<b>For the remainder of the campaign, each investigator cannot include Alejandro Vela or Ichtaca in his or
            her deck. Anytime an investigator would be given the option to include either of them, each
            investigator earns 2 experience instead.</b></string>


    <!--Scenario setup-->
    <string name="untamed_sets">The Untamed Wilds, Rainforest, Serpents, Expedition, Guardians of Time, Agents of
        Yig, Poison, and Ancient Evils.</string>
    <string name="untamed_locations">Put the Expedition Camp into play.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play at the Expedition Camp.\n</string>
    <string name="untamed_set_aside"> The three single-sided <b><i>Ruins</i></b> locations, the <i>Agents of Yig</i>
        encounter set, the four Poisoned weaknesses, the Alejandro Vela asset, and the Ichtaca enemy.\n
        \nThe <i>Agents of Yig</i> encounter set can be identified by this icon:</string>
    <string name="untamed_additional">Create the exploration deck. This is done by taking the five single-sided
        <b><i>Jungle</i></b> locations and shuffling them together, along with one copy each of the following
        treachery cards: Lost in the Wilds, Overgrowth, Snake Bite, Low on Supplies, and Arrows from the Trees.</string>
    <string name="untamed_additional_lead">Choose one of Ursula Downs, Leo Anderson or Monterey Jack to be the
        expedition leader. That investigator begins Scenarios I and II as the lead investigator.\n</string>

    <string name="eztli_sets">The Doom of Eztli, Agents of Yig, Yig’s Venom, Temporal Flux, Deadly Traps, Forgotten
        Ruins, Poison, and Chilling Cold.</string>
    <string name="eztli_locations">Put the Entryway into play.\n
        \nEach investigator begins play in the Entryway.\n</string>
    <string name="eztli_set_aside">The Harbinger of Valusia enemy, the Chamber of Time location, the Relic of Ages
        asset, and each Poisoned weakness that is not already in an investigator’s deck.\n</string>
    <string name="eztli_additional">Create the exploration deck. This is done by taking the five single-sided <b><i>
        Ancient</i></b> locations and shuffling them together, along with one copy each of the following treachery
        cards: Ill Omen, Deep Dark, Final Mistake, Entombed, and Crypt Chill.</string>
    <string name="eztli_additional_place">Place</string>
    <string name="eztli_additional_doom_single">doom on the Entryway.\n\n</string>
    <string name="eztli_additional_doom_multiple">doom on the Entryway.\n\n</string>
    <string name="eztli_low_rations_single_investigator">investigator begins the scenario with 3 fewer
        resources.\n\n</string>
    <string name="eztli_low_rations_multiple_investigators">investigators begin the scenario with 3 fewer
        resources.\n\n</string>
    <string name="eztli_additional_lead">Whichever one of Ursula Downs, Leo Anderson or Monterey Jack was chosen to be
        the expedition leader in Scenario I begins Scenario II as the lead investigator.</string>

    <string name="threads_sets">Threads of Fate, Pnakotic Brotherhood, The Midnight Masks, Locked Doors, Nightgaunts,
        and Dark Cult.\n
    \nWhen gathering The Midnight Masks encounter set, only gather the 5 treachery cards (2x False Lead and 3x
        Hunting Shadow) and the following locations: Northside, Downtown (First Bank of Arkham), Easttown,
        Miskatonic University, and Rivertown.</string>
    <string name="threads_locations">Put Northside, Downtown, Easttown, Miskatonic University, Rivertown, Velma’s
        Diner, and Curiositie Shoppe into play.\n
    \nEach investigator begins play in Rivertown.\n</string>
    <string name="threads_set_aside">The Town Hall location, the Ichtaca (The Forgotten Guardian) asset, and the
        Expedition Journal.\n
    \nBefore drawing opening hands, search the collection and each player’s deck for Alejandro Vela and Relic of Ages,
        and set them aside, out of play.\n</string>
    <string name="threads_additional_one">Remove the following act cards from the “a/b” act deck:\n
    \n\t\u2022 Harlan Is in Danger!, both copies of Harlan’s Curse, and one of the two copies of At the Exhibit, at
        random.\n
    \nThe investigators must choose one of the following options, and adjust the contents of the “c/d” act deck
        accordingly:\n
    \n\t\u2022 If you wish to go to the police to inform them about Alejandro’s disappearance, remove the following act
        cards from the “c/d” deck: Search for Alejandro, both copies of Friends in High Places, and one of the two
        copies of At the Station, at random.\n
    \n\t\u2022 If you wish to look for Alejandro on your own, remove the following act cards from the “c/d” deck, instead:
        Missing Persons, both copies of At the Station, and one of the two copies of Friends in High Places, at
        random.\n
    \nRemove the following cards from the “e/f” act deck:\n
    \n\t\u2022 Trial of the Huntress, both copies of The Cave of Darkness, and one of the two copies of Strange Relics, at
        random.\n</string>
    <string name="threads_additional_two">Remove the following act cards from the “a/b” act deck:\n
    \n\t\u2022 Harlan Is in Danger!, both copies of Harlan’s Curse, and one of the two copies of At the Exhibit, at
        random.\n
    \nThe investigators must choose one of the following options, and adjust the contents of the “c/d” act deck
        accordingly:\n
    \n\t\u2022 If you wish to go to the police to inform them about Alejandro’s disappearance, remove the following act
        cards from the “c/d” deck: Search for Alejandro, both copies of Friends in High Places, and one of the two
        copies of At the Station, at random.\n
    \n\t\u2022 If you wish to look for Alejandro on your own, remove the following act cards from the “c/d” deck, instead:
        Missing Persons, both copies of At the Station, and one of the two copies of Friends in High Places, at
        random.\n
    \nRemove the following cards from the “e/f” act deck:\n
    \n\t\u2022 The Guardian’s Inquiry, both copies of Strange Relics, and one of the two copies of The Cave of Darkness,
        at random.\n</string>
    <string name="threads_additional_three">Remove the following act cards from the “a/b” act deck:\n
    \n\t\u2022 The Relic Is Missing!, both copies of At the Exhibit, and one of the two copies of Harlan’s Curse, at
        random.\n
    \nThe investigators must choose one of the following options, and adjust the contents of the “c/d” act deck
        accordingly:\n
    \n\t\u2022 If you wish to go to the police to inform them about Alejandro’s disappearance, remove the following act
        cards from the “c/d” deck: Search for Alejandro, both copies of Friends in High Places, and one of the two
        copies of At the Station, at random.\n
    \n\t\u2022 If you wish to look for Alejandro on your own, remove the following act cards from the “c/d” deck, instead:
        Missing Persons, both copies of At the Station, and one of the two copies of Friends in High Places, at
        random.\n
    \nRemove the following cards from the “e/f” act deck:\n
    \n\t\u2022 Trial of the Huntress, both copies of The Cave of Darkness, and one of the two copies of Strange Relics, at
        random.\n</string>
    <string name="threads_additional_four">Remove the following act cards from the “a/b” act deck:\n
    \n\t\u2022 The Relic Is Missing!, both copies of At the Exhibit, and one of the two copies of Harlan’s Curse, at
        random.\n
    \nThe investigators must choose one of the following options, and adjust the contents of the “c/d” act deck
        accordingly:\n
    \n\t\u2022 If you wish to go to the police to inform them about Alejandro’s disappearance, remove the following act
        cards from the “c/d” deck: Search for Alejandro, both copies of Friends in High Places, and one of the two
        copies of At the Station, at random.\n
    \n\t\u2022 If you wish to look for Alejandro on your own, remove the following act cards from the “c/d” deck, instead:
        Missing Persons, both copies of At the Station, and one of the two copies of Friends in High Places, at
        random.\n
    \nRemove the following cards from the “e/f” act deck:\n
    \n\t\u2022 The Guardian’s Inquiry, both copies of Strange Relics, and one of the two copies of The Cave of Darkness,
        at random.\n</string>
    <string name="threads_rules_heading">Three Acts, Three Threads</string>
    <string name="threads_rules">This scenario contains three different act decks —an “a/b” deck, a “c/d” deck, and
        an “e/f ” deck. Each of these act decks is constructed separately, in numerical order, as usual. During the
        course of this scenario, all three of these act decks will be in play, and players may choose which acts to
        pursue and which to ignore. The text of all three acts is considered active at all times. You might not have
        time to accomplish all three tasks, so choose which leads you wish to pursue wisely!</string>


    <!--Scenario resolutions-->
    <string name="untamed_no_resolution">Wednesday, July 1st, 1925\n
    \nI still have no idea how we made it back to camp alive.\n
    \nThe jungle was more perilous than we could have possibly imagined. This may read like the ravings of a lunatic,
        but I cannot explain it any other way. Being lost in the jungle was no picnic, but that was the least of our
        worries. The rainforest was <i>guarded</i>. Guarded by unfathomable horrors: serpentine creatures driven by anger
        and hate, hunting us relentlessly.\n
    \nPerhaps just as deadly were the human natives of the rainforest. They appeared to be Aztec warriors as far as
        dress and speech were concerned. Despite the conquering of the Aztec people hundreds of years ago, these
        warriors somehow survived. How they managed to remain undiscovered this long is beyond us. I thought
        Alejandro would be excited to learn more about them, but he was more disturbed than fascinated. I suppose he
        has a right to be incredulous. Nothing about this expedition makes sense.\n
    \nThe serpent creatures chased us for what seemed like days. Finally we were able to find our way back to camp,
        but the price was steep. We had lost all progress we had made, and many of us were injured or afflicted by
        serpent venom. We have no choice but to send runners to the nearest city for additional supplies and to wait
        and recover from our wounds.</string>
    <string name="untamed_resolution_one">Thursday, July 2nd, 1925\n
    \nSomehow, after much toil and many hours of exploration we found the ruins that Alejandro sought, though we
        scarcely could have been ready for what we encountered in the wilds of the jungle. The rainforest was
        <i>guarded</i>. Guarded by unfathomable horrors: serpentine creatures driven by anger and hate. They hunted us
        relentlessly, wielding primitive weaponry and communicating in sharp hisses.\n
    \nPerhaps just as deadly were the human natives of the rainforest. They appeared to be Aztec warriors as far as
        dress and speech were concerned. Despite the conquering of the Aztec people hundreds of years ago, these
        warriors somehow survived. How they managed to remain undiscovered this long is beyond us. The warrior named
        Ichtaca was particularly intriguing. We were able to defuse the initial encounter with her, and surprisingly,
        she helped guide us through the jungle, only to disappear mysteriously when we reached the ruins. I have a
        feeling we have not seen the last of her.\n
    \nAlejandro did not agree with our decision to trust the Eztli warriors. He’s decided to stay at camp until
        further notice, disturbed as he is by their presence. I thought he would be excited to learn more about them,
        but I expect this discovery defies even his broad-minded theories. I suppose he has a right to be
        distrustful. Nothing about this expedition makes sense.\n
    \nWe have cleared a route to what Alejandro believes is the main temple of the ruins. There is little time to
        rest. The serpent creatures seem intent on stopping us, so we cannot tarry any longer than necessary. Soon we
        will enter the ruins to see what secrets they hide.</string>
    <string name="untamed_resolution_two">Thursday, July 2nd, 1925\n
    \nSomehow, after much toil and many hours of exploration, we found the ruins that Alejandro sought, though we
        scarcely could have been ready for what we encountered in the wilds of the jungle. The rainforest was <i>
            guarded</i>. Guarded by unfathomable horrors: serpentine creatures driven by anger and hate. They hunted
        us relentlessly, wielding primitive weaponry and communicating in sharp hisses.\n
    \nPerhaps just as deadly were the human natives of the rainforest. They appeared to be Aztec warriors as far as
        dress and speech were concerned. Despite the conquering of the Aztec people hundreds of years ago, these
        warriors somehow survived. How they managed to remain undiscovered this long is beyond us. I thought
        Alejandro would be excited to learn more about them, but he shared our alarm. We managed to fend off and
        interrogate their leader, a warrior named Ichtaca. Before she fled, she warned us to not go near the ruins.
        Unfortunately for her, we refuse to go home empty-handed.\n
    \nWith Alejandro leading the way, we’ve cleared a route to what he believes is the main temple of the ruins.
        There is little time to rest. The serpent creatures seem intent on stopping us, so we cannot tarry any longer
        than necessary. Soon we will enter the ruins to see what secrets they hide.\n
    \n<b>Any one investigator may choose to add Alejandro Vela to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="untamed_add_alejandro"><b>Any one investigator may choose to add Alejandro Vela to his or her deck.</b></string>

    <string name="eztli_resolution_one">(The following is scrawled below the previous journal entry.)\n
    \nThe outside of the temple ruins appeared Aztec in origin, but once we breached the interior, it became clear
        that these buildings had a very different and inhuman origin. The ruins were alive. The grooves in the walls
        were illuminated as though powered by electricity, and a faint hum of energy reverberated throughout the
        halls. In spite of the serpent creatures, we were able to reach a hidden passage that led deeper underground.\n
    \nIn the central chamber of these underground halls, we found our prize: a steel orb of unknown origin, gently
        humming and glowing with a dim blue light. It was attached delicately to a bronze frame, appearing almost
        religious in its significance, and we knew it could not have been made by the Aztecs.\n
    \nWith the artifact in tow, we fled the ruins. The building had started to crumble around us, as though the orb
        was the only thing keeping it standing. Had it been powering the ruins, like a battery? What exactly was this
        device that the serpents guarded so fervently?\n
    \nMaria was waiting for us with the trucks when we finally reached the northern edge of the rainforest. We’re
        getting the hell out of this serpent-infested jungle while we still can.\n
    \n<b>One investigator must add the Relic of Ages to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="eztli_resolution_one_defeated_one"><b>Defeated investigators:</b>\n
        \nThe temple shakes with the ferocity of an earthquake, causing you to collapse to the ground. Serpent
        creatures emerge from the shadows around you, surrounding you completely. The thought, “<i>This is how it
            ends</i>,”
        flashes through your mind. For a moment, you contemplate the absurdity of your death. You can only hope that
        nobody else will be foolish enough to try to explore these forsaken ruins.\n
        \nThe creatures are upon you before you have time to react. You scream in agony as you are skewered by
        razor-sharp spears.\n
        \n<b>Each investigator who was defeated is killed.</b>\n
        \n<b>Surviving investigators:</b>\n
    \n(The following is scrawled below the previous journal entry.)\n
    \nThe outside of the temple ruins appeared Aztec in origin, but once we breached the interior, it became clear
        that these buildings had a very different and inhuman origin. The ruins were alive. The grooves in the walls
        were illuminated as though powered by electricity, and a faint hum of energy reverberated throughout the
        halls. In spite of the serpent creatures, we were able to reach a hidden passage that led deeper underground.\n
    \nIn the central chamber of these underground halls, we found our prize: a steel orb of unknown origin, gently
        humming and glowing with a dim blue light. It was attached delicately to a bronze frame, appearing almost
        religious in its significance, and we knew it could not have been made by the Aztecs.\n
    \nWith the artifact in tow, we fled the ruins. The building had started to crumble around us, as though the orb
        was the only thing keeping it standing. Had it been powering the ruins, like a battery? What exactly was this
        device that the serpents guarded so fervently?\n
    \nMaria was waiting for us with the trucks when we finally reached the northern edge of the rainforest. We’re
        getting the hell out of this serpent-infested jungle while we still can.\n
    \n<b>One investigator must add the Relic of Ages to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="eztli_resolution_one_defeated_two"><b>Defeated investigators:</b>\n
        \nThe temple shakes with the ferocity of an earthquake, causing you to collapse to the ground. Serpent
        creatures emerge from the shadows around you, surrounding you completely. The thought, “<i>This is how it
            ends</i>,”
        flashes through your mind. For a moment, you contemplate the absurdity of your death. You can only hope that
        nobody else will be foolish enough to try to explore these forsaken ruins.\n
        \nSuddenly, a distant voice hisses to the others, and the serpents tentatively retreat into the darkness. You
        run for your life, not taking any chances.\n
        \n<b>Surviving investigators:</b>\n
    \n(The following is scrawled below the previous journal entry.)\n
    \nThe outside of the temple ruins appeared Aztec in origin, but once we breached the interior, it became clear
        that these buildings had a very different and inhuman origin. The ruins were alive. The grooves in the walls
        were illuminated as though powered by electricity, and a faint hum of energy reverberated throughout the
        halls. In spite of the serpent creatures, we were able to reach a hidden passage that led deeper underground.\n
    \nIn the central chamber of these underground halls, we found our prize: a steel orb of unknown origin, gently
        humming and glowing with a dim blue light. It was attached delicately to a bronze frame, appearing almost
        religious in its significance, and we knew it could not have been made by the Aztecs.\n
    \nWith the artifact in tow, we fled the ruins. The building had started to crumble around us, as though the orb
        was the only thing keeping it standing. Had it been powering the ruins, like a battery? What exactly was this
        device that the serpents guarded so fervently?\n
    \nMaria was waiting for us with the trucks when we finally reached the northern edge of the rainforest. We’re
        getting the hell out of this serpent-infested jungle while we still can.\n
    \n<b>One investigator must add the Relic of Ages to his or her deck.</b></string>
    <string name="eztli_resolution_two">The temple shakes with the ferocity of an earthquake, causing you to collapse to the ground. Serpent
        creatures emerge from the shadows around you, surrounding you completely. The thought, “<i>This is how it
            ends</i>,”
        flashes through your mind. For a moment, you contemplate the absurdity of your death. You can only hope that
        nobody else will be foolish enough to try to explore these forsaken ruins.\n
        \nThe creatures are upon you before you have time to react. You scream in agony as you are skewered by
        razor-sharp spears.\n
        \n<b>Each investigator is killed.</b>\n
        \n(The following is scrawled below the previous journal entry.)\n
    \nIt is not in my nature to leave a thing unfinished. For the sake of my fallen comrades, I have taken it upon
        myself to record the remainder of our expedition in this journal.\n
    \nThe others never made it out of the temple. I convinced two of the other members of the expedition, José and
        Andrea, to venture in after the others…But now I fear a terrible fate has befallen them, as well.\n
    \nThankfully, my gambit was worthwhile. While José and Andrea searched for the others, I snuck into the temple
        and took a different route. Having seen what we have seen, knowing what we know now, I couldn’t have
        returned to the university without evidence of our discovery. While the serpent creatures were distracted, I
        was able to reach a hidden passageway that led deeper underground.\n
    \nIn the central chamber of these underground halls, I found the device. The orb was made of an unnatural steel,
        attached delicately to its bronze frame. It pulsed with power in my hands and glowed with a dim blue light.
        Any fool could tell that it was not made by the Aztecs, but the other members of the expedition could not
        even begin to understand its true significance. The ruins started to crumble around me as I left, but it
        mattered not. The relic was all that mattered now.\n
    \nWith the artifact in tow, I returned to camp and told the others it was time to depart. Maria was waiting for
        us with the trucks when we finally reached the northern edge of the jungle. Now we are headed to Texas, where
        we will cross the border into the United States.\n
    \nIt is a shame what happened to the others. Their sacrifice will not be in vain. Now, my work can continue.\n
    \n– Alejandro Vela</string>
    <string name="eztli_resolution_three">(The following is scrawled below the previous journal entry.)\n
    \nThis was a mistake. This was all a terrible mistake. We escaped the temple with our lives, but not a moment too
        soon. The ruins were alive. It was as though the walls knew of our intrusion, hated us for our presence.
        Wanted us out. Wanted us dead. We have gathered outside the temple where José is waiting for us. Alejandro,
        unwilling to return home empty-handed, wants us to go back inside. We must decide what to do next.</string>
    <string name="eztli_resolution_three_defeated_one"><b>Defeated investigators:</b>\n
        \nThe temple shakes with the ferocity of an earthquake, causing you to collapse to the ground. Serpent
        creatures emerge from the shadows around you, surrounding you completely. The thought, “<i>This is how it
            ends</i>,”
        flashes through your mind. For a moment, you contemplate the absurdity of your death. You can only hope that
        nobody else will be foolish enough to try to explore these forsaken ruins.\n
        \nThe creatures are upon you before you have time to react. You scream in agony as you are skewered by
        razor-sharp spears.\n
        \n<b>Each investigator who was defeated is killed.</b>\n
        \n<b>Surviving investigators:</b>\n</string>
    \n(The following is scrawled below the previous journal entry.)\n
    \nThis was a mistake. This was all a terrible mistake. We escaped the temple with our lives, but not a moment too
    soon. The ruins were alive. It was as though the walls knew of our intrusion, hated us for our presence.
    Wanted us out. Wanted us dead. We have gathered outside the temple where José is waiting for us. Alejandro,
    unwilling to return home empty-handed, wants us to go back inside. We must decide what to do next.
    <string name="eztli_resolution_three_defeated_two"><b>Defeated investigators:</b>\n
        \nThe temple shakes with the ferocity of an earthquake, causing you to collapse to the ground. Serpent
        creatures emerge from the shadows around you, surrounding you completely. The thought, “<i>This is how it
            ends</i>,”
        flashes through your mind. For a moment, you contemplate the absurdity of your death. You can only hope that
        nobody else will be foolish enough to try to explore these forsaken ruins.\n
        \nSuddenly, a distant voice hisses to the others, and the serpents tentatively retreat into the darkness. You
        run for your life, not taking any chances.\n
        \n<b>Surviving investigators:</b>\n
    \n(The following is scrawled below the previous journal entry.)\n
    \nThis was a mistake. This was all a terrible mistake. We escaped the temple with our lives, but not a moment too
        soon. The ruins were alive. It was as though the walls knew of our intrusion, hated us for our presence.
        Wanted us out. Wanted us dead. We have gathered outside the temple where José is waiting for us. Alejandro,
        unwilling to return home empty-handed, wants us to go back inside. We must decide what to do next.</string>
    <string name="eztli_resolution_four">(The following is scrawled below the previous journal entry.)\n
    \nWe’ve made our decision. Alejandro is right: we’ve come too far to back down now. Our plan is to regroup and
        head back into the temple once more. Even from here, we can tell that the layout of the temple has warped and
        changed. The ruins seem to have reset to their dormant state. With any luck, we’ll make it out this
        time…\n
    \n<b>The investigators must replay Scenario II: The Doom of Eztli.</b></string>
    <string name="eztli_resolution_five">(The following is scrawled below the previous journal entry.)\n
    \nWe made our decision. There was no way we were going back into that deathtrap. Thankfully, there was another
        way. José had brought some TNT from the trucks, and there was more than enough to level the damned place.\n
    \nThat night, we put on a hell of a fireworks show. The jungle protested. Birds scattered into the sky, the
        ground rumbled, and hateful snarls surrounded our camp. But the dynamite did its job. Once the dust settled,
        we began sifting through the debris in search of anything with historical or cultural significance we could
        bring back to Arkham.\n
    \nJosé was the first to notice the blue light peeking out from underneath the remains of the temple. The rays
        grew in intensity with each passing moment. As we started clearing the rubble in order to discover the source
        of the light, there was a sudden flash, and the debris at the center of the ruins scattered. A steel orb of
        unknown origin lay on top of the rubble, gently humming. It was attached delicately to a bronze frame,
        appearing almost religious in its significance. The blue glow emanating from the device dimmed as I touched
        it. There was no way a device like this was built by the Aztecs.\n
    \nWith the artifact in tow, we left the smoldering temple behind us. We had outstayed our welcome in this
        rainforest, and we knew it. Around us, the jungle hissed. The ground slithered and crawled with snakes. In
        the darkness, we heard shouts in a language we could not understand. There was no time to pack up camp; we
        ran as soon as we had the chance. Andrea was struck in her throat by a black-feathered arrow, her startled
        scream captured in grim perpetuity. José was grabbed by a giant boa as we fled north into the river canyon.
        His neck snapped before we could reach him.\n
    \nMaria was waiting for us with the trucks when we finally reached the northern edge of the jungle. We didn’t
        stop until we crossed into Mexico City. Even now I do not feel safe: who could, after seeing what we have
        seen?\n
    \nTo hell with the Eztli and to hell with this forsaken place.\n
    \n<b>One investigator must add the Relic of Ages to his or her deck.</b></string>

</resources>